Um…
[Sayaka]
What should we do?
The Rindou Festival is this weekend.
[Megumi]
Assuming Kozue can overcome her cold by then…
I-I’ll nurse her back to health, no matter what!
[Kaho]
I understand how you feel, but you shouldn’t be the only one with that responsibility.
[Rurino]
Why don’t we look after her in shifts?
Alright, thanks, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Other than that…
[Sayaka]
there’s still putting together the practice schedule for the next few days,
as well as communicating with other clubs and the school.
[Sayaka]
Kozue-senpai’s been doing a lot of work for us, hasn’t she…?
Kozue-senpai the Great…
[Kaho]
It seems that this is all the work that needs to be sorted out before the festival.
[Sayaka]
…Alright, I got it.
[Tsuzuri]
…Tsuzuri-senpai?
[Sayaka]
I’ll be…
[Tsuzuri]
the acting president.
Huh!?
[Kaho & Sayaka & Rurino & Megumi]
Kozu’s been working so hard all this time…
[Tsuzuri]
and now I will continue on in her stead.
Surely she will be smiling down on us, from wherever she is.
[Tsuzuri]
Stop making it sound like she’s already gone!
[Kaho]
But you know, she has been with Kozue-senpai the longest, right?
[Rurino]
Maybe it could work?
Hold it.
[Megumi]
Megu-chan?
[Rurino]
Wait, I think I know what you’re gonna say next.
If you need an acting president…
[Megumi]
in other words, our next leader, then that should be me!
Were you right?
[Kaho]
Yep.
[Rurino]
Hey! You two, react harder!
[Megumi]
Why don’t I hear some “ooh!”s and “so true!”s from you!?
I won’t lose, Megu.
[Tsuzuri]
…Hmph.
[Megumi]
So you’re not giving up, Tsuzuri.
You’ve changed.
[Megumi]
That’s because I’ve grown.
[Tsuzuri]
What’s the right thing to do here…?
[Sayaka]
Hmm… I mean, if we’re looking for a leader,
[Rurino]
I don’t think Megu-chan would be a bad choice, but…
But?
[Kaho]
Since we’re looking for someone to fill in for Kozue-senpai,
[Rurino]
they’d have to do all the club president work she does, right?
…Megu-chan’s a little…
[Rurino]
Ruri-chan!?
[Megumi]
I-I have an idea! Why don’t both of you try it out!?
[Kaho]
I know about how much work Kozue-senpai does!
I’ve watched her from the sidelines plenty of times!
[Kaho]
Sure. I accept.
[Tsuzuri]
We’ll see who the better leader is!
[Megumi]
Wait, is this a competition now!?
[Sayaka]
Strange.
[Tsuzuri]
It’s wrong.
[Megumi]
Megu-chan, let’s work toward improving your reading skills…
[Rurino]
I can read just fine!
[Megumi]
It’s this language’s fault for not spelling things the way they’re read, right, Ruri-chan!?
Huh!? Y-Yeah…
[Rurino]
M-Maybe it’d help me very thank you understand…?
And as for you, Tsuzuri-senpai…
[Sayaka]
I don’t think they’ll lend us the practice space if our request just says “practice”…
Maybe I should’ve gone with “rehearsal”, then…
[Tsuzuri]
This won’t be solved just by using a more complicated word…
[Sayaka]
Grr…
[Megumi]
Fine, then who here’s gonna take Kozue’s place!?
Sorry, Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
Guess I’m just not meant to be like you.
Kozue-senpai’s place…
[Sayaka]
huh?
Yeah!
[Megumi]
Filling out all these forms, setting up the practice schedule, and making sure everyone stays focused!
And most of all…
[Sayaka]
someone who can lead us all.
Can’t do it.
[Rurino]
L-Looks like I’ll have to do it…!
[Kaho]
T-That sounds like it would be very difficult.
[Sayaka]
Not only do you have to take care of Kozue-senpai,
you’re also the de facto leader of Cerise Bouquet for now…
[Sayaka]
Oof. B-But I wanna do everything I can…!
[Kaho]
Very well.
[Sayaka]
Huh?
[Kaho]
It is imperative that we all cooperate with each other while Kozue-senpai isn’t available.
[Sayaka]
To that end, I think I would be the least obtrusive candidate…
I-I see…
[Rurino]
I’m so sorry, Sayaka-chan…! I’ll help however I can…!
It really isn’t such a big deal!
[Sayaka]
Um… Tsuzuri-senpai, Megumi-senpai?
What do you two think?
[Sayaka]
Well, if you’re volunteering to…
[Megumi]
Sure. You’re always so helpful, Saya.
[Tsuzuri]
Thank you very much.
[Sayaka]
If everyone accepts, then I, Murano Sayaka,
accept the responsibilities of the provisional presidential position.
[Sayaka]
I’ll do my best!
Sayaka-chaaan!
[Rurino]
One of the committee members is asking if you have the club meeting form filled out!
Yes! Right here!
[Sayaka]
Ooh! Very punctual!
[Rurino]
Adding in all of our subunits’ performances, I think we should reserve the festival stage for an hour.
[Megumi]
Understood.
[Sayaka]
Then, for the application form, I’ll write… hm…
In order for the School Idol Club to emphasize its purpose, and so that each school idol can represent her respective subunit…
[Sayaka]
Huh!? You already came up with all that!?
[Megumi]
For today’s practice, in addition to our usual agenda,
[Sayaka]
we must prepare for our upcoming
performance at the Rindou Festival.
[Sayaka]
Therefore, I’ve made some adjustments to Kozue-senpai’s usual practice schedule.
Got it! What do you need me to do?
[Kaho]
Right, first of all…
[Sayaka]
Since Cerise Bouquet is in a rough situation,
[Tsuzuri]
I’ll be watching over Saya and Kaho too.
Ooh!
[Kaho]
…”too”?
The songs and lyrics, too.
[Tsuzuri]
I’m a little different from Kozu, but I’ll help as much as I can.
Tsuzuri-senpai~
[Kaho]
Thank you very much!!
No prob.
[Tsuzuri]
Saya said you looked like you were in trouble, so she wanted to do what she could.
Did you really need to say that part out loud!?
[Sayaka]
Thank you too, Sayaka-chan!!
[Kaho]
N-No worries.
[Sayaka]
Maaan, you’re like the perfect leader!
[Rurino]
Madam President!
I think you’re working really hard.
[Megumi]
You can spell good, too…
Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
Listen!
[Sayaka]
I just think that we should do what we can, together!
No need to be humble, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
Oh, and I have a message for you from Kozue-senpai.
She said, “You can trust Sayaka-san. If there’s any trouble, don’t forget to contact me.”
[Kaho]
A-Ahaha…
[Sayaka]
Please also tell Kozue-senpai that I’ll be doing my best…
Saya.
[Tsuzuri]
Y-Yes!
[Sayaka]
I’m counting on you.
[Tsuzuri]
Maybe…
[Sayaka]
I really am cut out for this…