Pleeease! Come waaatch!
[Rurino]
Kaho-chan, Sayaka-chan, I only have a little more!
Oh, wow, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
I still have a lot left!
Oh, that’s not it! I meant my battery!
[Rurino]
Oh, no!!!
[Kaho]
Ah, please come watch!
We’re from the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
[Kaho]
We’re gonna hold the best performance ever at our Rindou Festival, so we hope you’ll be there!
U-Uhhhh…
[Sayaka]
Why…
why these…
[Sayaka]
these…
Saaa-yaaa-kaaa-chaaan!
[Kaho]
C’mon, don’t be so shy! Give it everything you’ve got!
You look reeeally cute!
[Kaho]
Yeah, Sayaka-chan!
[Rurino]
Have confidence! You’re super cute!
T-Thank you very much…
[Sayaka]
B-But, do I really need this sash!?
You do! Definitely! Everyone needs to see it!
[Sayaka]
This is what we’re deciding to emphasize!?
–Ah, yes! Please take this!
[Sayaka]
It’s information on the upcoming Hasunosora Rindou Festival!
Hope to see you there!
[Rurino]
Ah… but this was a really nice idea, Kaho-chan.
Yeah!
[Kaho]
When I went with Kozue-senpai to help out at that cafe, the staff told us that we looked really good in these!
Then I asked if we could borrow those cute uniforms again someday!
[Kaho]
Y-You sure do commit to things, huh…
[Sayaka]
I figured that since we were gonna be performing live, I want a lot of people to come watch!
[Kaho]
I want everyone to see me wearing costumes like these on stage so we can all blossom into smiles!
Please come watch!
[Kaho]
We’re from the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
We’ll definitely be holding a performance!
[Kaho]
…Thank you very much! I’ll do my best!
We want to make the Rindou Festival the best thing ever!
[Kaho]
Yeah, thank you!
Phew…
[Kaho]
Huh? What’s up, you two?
Nothing…
[Sayaka]
I just thought, you were really…
You were shining super bright, Kaho-chan!
[Rurino]
Ooh, really~!? Thanks!
[Kaho]
But, I don’t really get it.
I’m not like Sayaka-chan.
[Kaho]
I still don’t really know what’s the point of handing out these flyers!
No…
[Sayaka]
I think you’re fine just the way you are now.
Huh?
[Kaho]
What do you mean, Sayaka-chan?
[Rurino]
Even back when we first met…
[Sayaka]
Kaho-san’s been saying she wants everyone to watch her so she can blossom…
It left quite an impression on me.
[Sayaka]
Oh…
[Kaho]
Oh, that’s what you mean.
I became a school idol because I wanted to blossom!
[Kaho]
And that’s why I want to perform at the Rindou Festival, and definitely why I want to perform at Love Live!
I want to blossom! Right there, on stage! In front of everyone!
[Kaho]
You want to perform at Love Live! so you can blossom… huh…
[Rurino]
Ehehe. I don’t know if this is it,
[Kaho]
but maybe that was the purpose Sayaka-chan
mentioned the student council president had?
[Kaho]
Not why the second-years want to perform in Love Live!, but why we do…
[Sayaka]
I’m not sure I have one of those.
[Rurino]
But if the president wants us to look for our own reasons to perform in Love Live!, then…
But again, I might be wrong!
[Kaho]
…Let’s look for the answer while we hand out these flyers! Yeah!?
O-Okay…!
[Sayaka]
Y-yeeah…
[Rurino]
This is bad, Kaho-san!
[Sayaka]
Rurino-san’s battery…!
Hurry!!!
[Kaho]