P-Please! H-Hasunosora Girls’ High School! Will be holding!
[Sayaka]
Its Rindou Festival! We hope you’ll be there!
Sayaka-chan, Sayaka-chan! Say stuff about us, too!
[Kaho]
Yeah, yeah! You know you want to, Sayaka-chan!
[Rurino]
Then, why don’t you two do it!?
[Sayaka]
‘Cause you’re the leader, Sayaka-chan.
[Rurino & Kaho]
Guuuh…!
[Sayaka]
Understood…!
We hope you’ll come to our Rindou Festival!
[Sayaka]
Because we the members of the Hasunosora School Idol Club…
will definitely hold a great performance!
[Sayaka]
We definitely, definitely will!!!
Yeah, yeah! You said it, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
Now there’s no way she’ll cancel our performance on us!
[Rurino]
Oh, come on!
[Sayaka]
How did my life even come to this!?
…Next week, the second of our three school festivals, the Rindou Festival, will finally be upon us.
[Kozue]
What’s with this menacing atomsphere…?
[Rurino]
It’s “atmosphere,” Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
But they kinda sound the same.
[Tsuzuri]
We’re having a serious discussion right now, Tsuzuri-senpai.
[Sayaka]
It seems things are proceeding the same way they always do.
[Kozue]
I expected everyone to be a bit more serious.
Is there something special about the Rindou Festival, Kozue-senpai?
[Kaho]
Ah… right.
[Kozue]
It’s somewhat difficult to explain, though…
Yeah, I was injured at last year’s Rindou Festival, after all.
[Megumi]
Hehe, you guys don’t need to look so stressed!
That goes for our first years…
[Megumi]
and you too, Kozue.
…Megumi.
[Kozue]
Right. The past is in the past. Now is the present.
We’re not the same as we were last year.
[Kozue]
Wouldn’t you say so, Tsuzuri?
Yeah. So much stuff happened.
[Tsuzuri]
Since we lost Megu.
Right…!
[Kozue]
That being said!
While for us, this year’s Rindou Festival is a second chance…
[Kozue]
There is something else equally as important!
Ooh! And that is…!?
[Rurino]
The upcoming Love Live! regional qualifiers!
[Kozue]
We’ll be using our once-a-year performance at the festival as our entry!
Love…!
[Kaho]
Live…!
[Sayaka]
…Is that what Megu-chan was talking about before?
[Rurino]
I think everyone’s talked about it!
[Megumi]
It’s the big school idol festival!
So the time has finally come…
[Sayaka]
We’re gonna be in… Love Live!
[Kaho]
Wow…
[Tsuzuri]
Why are you reacting like it’s your first time too…?
[Kozue]
But Kozue-senpai?
[Rurino]
What do you mean we’ll be using our performance at the Rindou Festival?
Ah, yes. Allow me to explain in more detail.
[Kozue]
Yes, please.
[Sayaka]
Now, most importantly, the Love Live! competition has three stages:
[Kozue]
the regional qualifiers, sectional qualifiers, and finally the national championship.
The regional qualifiers we will be soon entering are held through video submissions.
[Kozue]
Videos… huh?
[Sayaka]
Ah, I understand. So…
Correct. With how many school idols there are, there isn’t enough space in all the reserved venues.
[Kozue]
Therefore, they hold this round of the competition online.
Oh, right. A lot of school idols enter Love Live!.
[Tsuzuri]
It seems like you think this’ll be nice and fun, but it won’t be that easy!
[Megumi]
I didn’t want to bring this up, but last year I wasn’t able to qualify!
But that’s because you were injured, right?
[Rurino]
I guess.
[Megumi]
I mean, of course I always believe in myself, but…
Honestly, I couldn’t say that I’d advance even if I hadn’t injured myself.
[Megumi]
I’m serious when I say that the competition is fierce.
Oh… That tough, huh…?
[Rurino]
It’s exactly as Megumi says. The regional qualifiers are not to be taken lightly.
[Kozue]
If even one subunit advances, then Hasunosora will have a representative at the Hokuriku competition…
but…
[Kozue]
I want all of our subunits to advance past these qualifiers.
To do what we could not last year.
[Kozue]
…But what about the Hokuriku competition onwards?
[Sayaka]
We’ll worry about it then!
[Megumi]
Huh…?
[Sayaka]
Anyway.
[Kozue]
I want all of us to advance past the regional qualifiers, no matter what.
That’s why we’ll be using the Rindou Festival!
[Kozue]
…I get it!
[Kaho]
It’s something suuuper fun, just like the Nadeshiko Festival!
Exactly!
[Kozue]
I want to make the most of the energy going into the grand setting of the Rindou Festival and send it into our entry for the qualifier.
That’s our plan.
[Kozue]
Ooh! Using the Rindou Festival would be a great advantage!
[Rurino]
We’d be able to have everyone there for the festival come watch our performance, wouldn’t we!?
That sounds great!
[Kaho]
Alright, let’s do our best to get a ton of people!
Yeah!
[Rurino]
…Yeah?
Huh?
[Rurino]
But if we did that, then I’d be totally spent by the time the performance starts!
But now that I brought it up, I’ve gotta deliver!
[Rurino]
You don’t need to push yourself, okay!?
[Kaho]
It’ll be fine! You can just take the box on stage, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Didn’t I just say to take this seriously?
[Megumi]
There’s no way you want me to perform as
Fujishima Megumi, featuring Cardboard Box, do you?
[Megumi]
So energetic.
[Tsuzuri]
A-Ahaha…
[Sayaka]
Everyone, focus up! This isn’t the time for games!
[Kozue]
It’s not just Rurino-san.
Every one of us needs to make sure we stay healthy leading up to the festival!
[Kozue]
Starting today, we all need to take practice seriously so we can put on a perfect performance!
You all seem ready.
[Kozue]
I’m sure we can do it. All subunits advancing past the qualifiers…
and holding the perfect performance at the festival.
[Kozue]
With the weather getting colder, we all must be even more diligent to stay healthy!
Yeah!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Tsuzuri & Rurino & Megumi]
Don’t any of you dare catch a cold!
[Kozue]
Yeah!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Tsuzuri & Rurino & Megumi]
…I’m very sorry.
[Kozue]
I-It’s alright…!
[Kaho]
Good grief…
[Megumi]
after you stressed how important it was to not get sick.
Did you go and practice behind our backs?
[Megumi]
Ugh… There isn’t any excuse for this…
[Kozue]
But I stuck to our planned practice schedule.
And everything else?
[Tsuzuri]
…I had more presidential responsibilities as a result of the Rindou Festival.
[Kozue]
And then, I wanted to work on songwriting and fine-tuning the choreography…
I-I don’t really get it, but it sounds like you had a ton of work…
[Rurino]
So basically, you were practicing the same amount as usual,
[Megumi]
but you ended up doing more other stuff.
No wonder you turned out like this.
[Megumi]
I guess we never noticed because we don’t know how hard it is being the club president.
What’s her temperature?
[Tsuzuri]
39°C…
[Sayaka]
It’s still under 40, so I should be able to…
[Kozue]
Denied!
[Kaho]
Um, you guys should leave, too!
It’d be bad if we caught what she has!
[Kaho]
You’re right…
[Kozue]
if I spread what I have to you all…
Yeah, that’s right!
[Kaho]
We need you to rest and recover!
I’ll do everything I can to nurse you back to health! I’ve got this!
[Kaho]
I…
[Kozue]
“I”?
[Kaho]
I can’t believe myself!!!
[Kozue]
Ah.
Kozue-senpaaai!!
[Kaho]