Alright, my next class is in another room.
[Megumi]
At least music class can be pretty enjoyable–
Ah, Megumi. Perfect timing.
[Kozue]
Hm?
[Megumi]
Would you mind staying behind in the clubroom after practice this afternoon?
[Kozue]
Uh, okay…?
[Megumi]
Alright, I’ll see you later, then.
[Kozue]
S-Sure.
[Megumi]
…Huh? What did I do?
The wind is gentle today, so the clouds are relaxed.
[Tsuzuri]
I’m sure the night stars will be happy, too.
Night…
[Tsuzuri]
Hmmm…
Dark…
[Tsuzuri]
Dark, dark…
Light switch…
[Tsuzuri]
Mmm…
Futon…
[Tsuzuri]
I’m getting kinda sleepy.
Tsuzuri, could I have a moment?
[Kozue]
Sure. Do you feel sleepy too, Kozu?
[Tsuzuri]
I want to talk to you after our club meeting.
[Kozue]
Huh…?
[Tsuzuri]
That’s all. I’ll see you then.
[Kozue]
…Did I do something wrong again…?
[Tsuzuri]
Ah… the wind…
It’s gotten a little colder…
[Tsuzuri]
I think…
Thank you for staying behind, you two.
[Kozue]
…But why are both of you sitting so far away?
Well…
[Megumi]
We don’t know what you’re scolding us for…
[Tsuzuri]
Scolding?
[Kozue]
Am I supposed to be scolding you?
For what?
[Kozue]
Well, with the way you asked us, what else were we supposed to think!?
[Megumi]
Huh…?
[Kozue]
I thought I invited you here pretty normally…
Nope! It was exactly how the guidance counselor would do it!
[Megumi]
Definitely.
[Tsuzuri]
…Do you two get really called to the guidance office that often…?
[Kozue]
Never mind.
I asked you two to stay today because I wanted to discuss something less than pleasant…
[Kozue]
We really are getting scolded…
[Tsuzuri]
I have two sheets of paper here with me.
[Kozue]
…Are those withdrawal forms for me and Tsuzuri…!?
[Megumi]
…Ah! You’re planning on weeding out misbehaving club members!? Is that it!?
Deepest apologies. I will listen intently in class starting tomorrow.
[Tsuzuri]
Should I forget my textbooks, I will go back to the dorm to get it instead of just waving it off with an “Oh well.”
Those are all things you should already be doing, though…
[Kozue]
But nevertheless, it seems there’s been a misunderstanding.
What I wanted to talk about today was…
[Kozue]
The promise the three of us made…
[Tsuzuri]
…To go our separate ways and not interfere with each other after we withdrew from nationals.
[Megumi]
This is what the three of us decided after advancing beyond the Hokuriku qualifier.
[Kozue]
The paper that Megumi wrote, and that we all signed our names on.
Last year I truly believed that this was the best path forward.
[Kozue]
Megumi was injured, and we lost Sachi-senpai.
And in my desire to protect the club and advance past the sectional qualifier, I hurt Tsuzuri.
[Kozue]
We argued countless times in what we could only call clashes of ideas,
yet in reality, we were only pitting our egos against each other.
[Kozue]
This is the proof of our prior naïveté…
Our sapling certification, if you will.
[Kozue]
…I wanted to once again have an earnest discussion about this.
If there is anything you two have not yet told me, I want to hear it so I can come to terms with it.
[Kozue]
If I could have done things a little differently, a little better, then maybe…
What, you would have stopped me from getting injured?
[Megumi]
You would’ve stopped me from separating myself from the group for a year?
I…
[Kozue]
You’re so arrogant, Kozue.
[Megumi]
Megu…
[Tsuzuri]
The only cause of my injury was my injury.
[Megumi]
The only reason I couldn’t dance was because I couldn’t dance.
That’s it. There’s no hidden meaning behind those things.
[Megumi]
And despite all that, the two of you still helped with my rehab.
You cut into your practice time, and even your own personal time for me.
[Megumi]
That’s why I stopped being a school idol.
I decided that myself.
[Megumi]
You don’t see it?
Right there, on the text we signed our names on.
[Megumi]
Maybe you’re the club president now,
but to us, both the Kozue then and the Kozue now are just a classmate who’s a little more dependable than our other ones.
[Megumi]
And yet you still try to harbor our burdens, every single time.
It’s so irritating.
[Megumi]
…Megumi…
[Kozue]
I don’t think I have as much say on this as Megu.
[Tsuzuri]
It was my fault you forced yourself to do all those things.
When I think about what happened last year, it feels like my body’s sinking.
[Tsuzuri]
Like I’m going deeper into a dark ocean, and the light’s getting further away.
If this is what regrets are like, then I’ve always regretted it.
[Tsuzuri]
If only I talked to Kozu more…
Megu too.
[Tsuzuri]
Yeah.
[Megumi]
And maybe I could even take the role of president.
[Tsuzuri]
No, I think that’s a bit much…!
[Megumi]
…You two.
[Kozue]
Alright, enough with all this downer talk!
[Megumi]
The three of us were missing useful life experience, so things weren’t ideal!
That’s it! Any problems with that!?
[Megumi]
But…
[Kozue]
I said, no more!
[Megumi]
Do you plan on spending the rest of our lives apologizing for what happened last year!?
I’m happy the way things are now, so there’s no use reopening old wounds!
[Megumi]
I think you should learn how to take things more lightly, Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
Like a cloud.
Whether it’s your relationships with other people, or your studies, or your school idol work,
[Megumi]
you always treat everything the same.
If there’s something you can’t do, you keep at it until you can.
[Megumi]
You think you can’t do things because you’re not working hard enough.
T-That’s…
[Kozue]
Well, isn’t that the way it is?
If I were you, I’d give up after an hour.
[Megumi]
I’d give myself five seconds.
[Tsuzuri]
But…
[Kozue]
It upsets me, too.
When I’m not up to things,
[Kozue]
it always ends with someone sad.
If I could, I’d like to be as perfect as music is.
[Kozue]
Like a piece of sheet music, if even one aspect is missing, then it ceases to be perfect.
Tsuzuri, grab onto Kozue’s cheeks and pull!
[Megumi]
Nyoooom.
[Tsuzuri]
Scyoosh me!?
(Excuse me!?)
[Kozue]
Now you’re no longer perfect!
[Megumi]
Far from ideal, eh!?
Come on! I was trying to have a serious conversation!
[Kozue]
…Good grief…
…But thank you.
[Kozue]
Everything feels a little lighter now.
Only a little?
[Tsuzuri]
Progress is progress.
[Megumi]
Kozue likes carrying everything on her shoulders, after all.
I don’t… think that’s true.
[Kozue]
So, what about this… sapling certification, you called it?
[Tsuzuri]
What do we do with it?
Hmmm, rip it up into a million tiny pieces and throw them away?
[Megumi]
If we don’t do anything with it, Kozue will probably frame it on her wall as a “warning” or something.
B-But, reflecting on one’s mistakes is important for personal growth…
[Kozue]
Wait, you seriously were gonna do it!?
[Megumi]
If you keep punishing yourself like that, you’ll sound like someone with one of those hobbies!
It’s not like I really was going to!
[Kozue]
Yeah. Anyway, let’s just take it home for now.
[Tsuzuri]
Having nothing around the school makes the stars look really pretty, huh?
[Megumi]
I appreciate this path back to the dorms.
[Kozue]
You can see a variety of different stars in each season.
Huh? Didn’t you say you had two papers earlier?
[Tsuzuri]
What was the other one?
I wasn’t just imagining it, was I?
[Tsuzuri]
…I didn’t forget about it.
[Kozue]
There just wasn’t a good time to show it to you.
An entry form for Love Live!
[Megumi]
It’s just like last year’s.
[Tsuzuri]
Naturally, things are different this year.
[Kozue]
Last year, only Tsuzuri and I were registered to perform.
This year, we’ve got six people! Three subunits!
[Megumi]
DOLLCHESTRA can perform.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s right.
[Kozue]
This year we can do what we really wanted to do.
Well, naturally, that isn’t to say that I didn’t learn anything from performing with Tsuzuri last year…
[Kozue]
but I digress.
The way you said that reminds me of Saya.
[Tsuzuri]
The day Mira-Cra Park! can change the world is finally here!
[Megumi]
Cerise Bouquet can surely rise the ranks and become the strongest of school idols.
[Kozue]
Just as I dreamed that day.
But no matter who wins or loses, no grudges, okay?
[Megumi]
Yes, of course.
[Kozue]
But Saya and I are the best.
[Tsuzuri]
Oh? Is our genius here calling her shot already~!?
[Megumi]
Sometimes I can’t tell if you two are each other’s best friends or worst enemies.
[Kozue]
…But the three of us have a truly irreplaceable bond.
If a single one of us were missing, we wouldn’t be the “Hasu Big Three,” after all.
[Kozue]
Hasu Big Three.
[Tsuzuri]
Tsuzuri…?
[Megumi]
I had a great idea.
[Tsuzuri]
Let’s fold a star.
Let’s do our best today as well!
[Kaho]
Low population density means a happy Ruri!
[Rurino]
Good morning.
[Sayaka]
I look forward to today’s club session.
Huh? What’s this origami star?
[Kaho]
Oh, you’re right…
[Rurino]
This wasn’t here yesterday, right?
That used to be a sapling.
[Tsuzuri]
But now, it’s a beautiful star.
Sayaka-chan, translation please!
[Rurino]
Huh!? Sorry, I don’t know, either!
[Sayaka]
And its name is the Hasu Big Three.
[Tsuzuri]
But there’s only one star!?
[Kaho]
…I mean, it sounds nice, but…
[Megumi]
I think it’s a great idea.
[Kozue]
Rather than destroying our past, we’ve turned it into a star.
…Heh, maybe.
[Megumi]
I think so.
[Kozue]
In any case… Everyone!
Let’s give today’s practice our best!
[Kozue]
Okaaay!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Tsuzuri & Rurino & Megumi]