Um…
[Kozue]
Let me say it one more time.
I sincerely apologize for all the trouble I caused.
[Kozue]
Huh, no, no, no!
[Kaho]
Look, it’s not like you can control when you catch a cold!
No, I definitely could have done better.
[Kozue]
This just proves I have gotten too lax with my personal health management.
As your club president, this is something I cannot forgive myself for.
[Kozue]
Whoa, she’s serious about this.
[Megumi]
Mad respect, Kozue-senpai…
[Rurino]
Ain’t no way I could live like that…
Why did you put it like that…?
[Sayaka]
In any case!
[Kozue]
I’m very sorry!
Ok.
[Tsuzuri]
Wait, are you sure we can say “ok” here!?
[Megumi]
What happens if we catch a cold ourselves!?
If we don’t accept her apology, she won’t stop.
[Tsuzuri]
I mean, I guess so.
[Megumi]
Let’s accept it to shut her up, then!
You two…!
[Kozue]
Alright, let’s calm down!
[Kaho]
Anyway, our performance today turned out great, didn’t it!
I… suppose.
[Kozue]
Speaking of which…
Sayaka-san.
[Kozue]
Huh? A-Ah, yes!
[Sayaka]
Thank you.
[Kozue]
This was all thanks to you.
Yeaaah. For real.
[Rurino]
Thank ya, Sayaka-sama~
Good work out there, Sayaka-sama.
[Megumi]
Wha–!? U-Um, what do you mean!?
[Sayaka]
You know what we mean!
[Kaho]
You being our acting leader really saved our performance!
Kaho-san…
[Sayaka]
No, I should thank you guys too.
Huh!? Can we really accept your thanks!?
[Rurino]
W-Why are you putting me on some sort of pedestal!?
[Sayaka]
Thank you, Sun Goddess Sayaka.
[Megumi]
That wasn’t an invitation!
[Sayaka]
You know, so much stuff happened while you were gone, Kozue-senpai.
[Kaho]
It seems so.
[Kozue]
I’d like to hear that story sometime later.
It seems like it was quite an exciting adventure.
[Kozue]
Yeah!
[Kaho]
…Actually, there was one thing I wanted to ask…
Yes?
[Kozue]
I was wondering about your relationship with the student council president.
[Kaho]
…Ah…
[Kozue]
Based on Tsuzuri and Megumi’s reactions, I presume?
Well…
[Kozue]
I’d say at this point it’s been about a year since she left the School Idol Club.
We all loved her very much, so it made us very sad when she left.
[Kozue]
But…
right, let’s look at things from her perspective.
[Kozue]
I’m sure that she had fun having the chance to be with her juniors after so long.
Sometime soon…
[Kozue]
perhaps we might face her as well…