…Hm. So you’re doing what you’re doing because you want to meet everyone’s expectations.
[Sachi]
That’s why you’re a school idol, then.
Yes.
[Sayaka]
I think that the expectations people have of me are why I chose to become a school idol and why I want to be one.
…I’d say you conveyed that sentiment perfectly.
[Sachi]
In that case…
[Sayaka]
that’s all I have to say.
I see.
[Sachi]
I see…
Um!
[Kaho]
Did Sayaka-chan pass your test!?
I’ve seen just how hard she’s worked for today’s performance!!
[Kaho]
The whole time Kozue-senpai was out sick, she filled in for her! She even handled our practice schedules!
Yeah, really!
[Rurino]
Not only that, she also said she’d show you her answer in today’s performance, and you saw how amazing she just was!
You saw it, didn’t you!?
[Rurino]
You two…
[Sayaka]
…Pass, huh? Did she pass?
[Sachi]
…hehe…
Huh?
[Kaho]
Na--hahahaha!
[Sachi]
She’s doing that evil laugh again!
[Rurino]
Hey, do you even remember what the test was supposed to be for, Sayaka?
[Sachi]
Huh? It was…
[Sayaka]
for permission to use the stage… right?
Wait, that…
[Sayaka]
…Finally get it?
[Sachi]
Besides, from the moment you stood up to me back then, I already knew you’d found your answer.
….O-Oh, come on…
[Kaho]
Oh, why not.
[Sachi]
I ought to say it for posterity.
–Sayaka, you pass the third test!
[Sachi]
…A-Ah…
[Sayaka]
Well isn’t that an unenthusiastic response.
[Sachi]
Oh, well!
Na–hahahaha!!
[Sachi]
G-Gah! You jerk!!
[Rurino]
This girl really is evil! Blegh!
[Kaho]
Oh, my. Sorry, sorry, did I take it too far?
[Sachi]
…Sachi-senpai.
[Sayaka]
Hm…?
[Sachi]
Thank you very much.
[Sayaka]
…Ahaha.
[Sachi]
To be honest, I was expecting you to react like Rurino and Kaho did.
No…
[Sayaka]
I think I finally get what me…
and the first-years as a whole need to improve on.
[Sayaka]
All of this really helped me understand everything.
…Well, if you really did figure all that out, it’s because of your own efforts.
[Sachi]
I had nothing to do with it.
I’m not in the School Idol Club anymore, after all.
[Sachi]
Be that as it may, you’re still our senior.
[Sayaka]
…Heh, guess so.
[Sachi]
Anyway… good luck.
Have fun with Love Live!
[Sachi]
I’ll try.
[Sayaka]
Alright, I’m gonna go now, Sachi-senpai.
…Hey, Sayaka.
[Sachi]
Yes?
[Sayaka]
I fully got the message that you want to meet everyone’s expectations.
[Sachi]
But why did you choose to convey that through a solo performance?
That’s…
[Sayaka]
You know what?
[Kaho]
I wanted to meet everyone’s expectations.
[Sayaka]
I wanted to feel their weight.
I could feel myself becoming stronger through other people’s expectations…
[Sayaka]
And since I noticed that…
…You thought it would be easiest to understand if you were to have those expectations solely on you.
[Sachi]
I see.
I see…
[Sachi]
Yes.
[Sayaka]
Yeah, I honestly think it was amazing…
[Sachi]
You really shone brightly up there.
Alright, you’ve been here long enough.
[Sachi]
You can go back to Tsuzuri and the others now.
…Alright.
[Sayaka]
Thank you very much, Sachi-senpai.
Yeah.
[Sachi]
Let’s go back, Rurino-san, Kaho-san…
[Sayaka]
Huh?
Battery died.
[Rurino]
…Hmhm, let’s go.
[Sayaka]
What a nice scene.
[Sachi]