Time for your second test, challengers…!
[Sachi]
Hmph! Well aren’t you having fun!
[Kaho]
Ahaha!
[Sachi]
If you want your venue, you’re gonna have to go through me!
Now, pass my tests!
[Sachi]
Grrrr…
[Rurino]
Oh? Are you going to devour me now?
[Sachi]
And how will that help you pass the tests???
Um, you need your box?
[Sachi]
There’s something I want even more than that right now…!
[Rurino]
Heh, right.
[Sachi]
You all seem pretty motivated right now, huh…
Alright then! I will unveil the test now!
[Sachi]
Your second test is…
School Idol Connect!
[Sachi]
School Idol Connect…?
[Kaho]
Wait, you mean SIC?
If we’re talking about the same SIC, then it’s where we upload our livestreams.
[Sayaka]
Right. It’s the same one you always use.
[Sachi]
Oh, you always use it, hm… Not bad…
Your test is to use that same app, and upload a video advertising the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
[Sachi]
A video?
[Kaho]
Not a stream?
The benefit of a video is the ability to convey your points in a short amount of time.
[Sachi]
Unlike a livestream, you have to think about what you want to say and how to sway people’s hearts to your cause.
Despite the villainous phrasing, that’s something entirely proper…!
[Sayaka]
Bwahahaha! How’s that!?
[Sachi]
You agree that you need to get yourselves out there before the Rindou Festival, don’t you?
Good luck!
[Sachi]
But it’s thanks to a certain someone’s “tests” that we’re in this situation in the first place!
[Rurino]
Na–hahaha!
[Sachi]
If you’re mad about it, get to it then!
If your performance at the festival isn’t exciting, then there’s no way you’ll get past the Love Live! qualifiers!
[Sachi]
U-Understood…
[Sayaka]
If that’s what you want, we’ll do it.
Yeah! We aren’t losing to you!
[Kaho]
We’ll show you, jerk!!
[Rurino]
Rurino-chan! You don’t need to be rude!!
[Kaho]
…Heh.
[Sachi]
Guess I should get to work too~
Alright, that should be… it!
[Kaho]
Does it look right?
Yes, this should be perfect.
[Sayaka]
If we set the phone here, it should be good.
Okay! Let’s get to recording~!
[Rurino]
…Well, as much as I’d like to say that…
Rurino-san?
[Sayaka]
Maaan… It’s just this whole advertising thing, y’know?
[Rurino]
Honestly, I dunno what I should say!
Yeah…
[Kaho]
The difference between videos and streams…
I don’t think I’ve ever really thought about it before.
[Kaho]
And when we record videos of our performances, there’s no need to really think about it since that’s all we’re recording.
[Sayaka]
And it’s Rurino-chan’s first school festival, too…
[Kaho]
Why don’t we start with Kaho-san and me, then?
[Sayaka]
I think I know what I want to say.
Of course, Kaho-san is free to agree or disagree, but I think having Rurino-san go last will help her come up with something.
[Sayaka]
Oh, that’d be really helpful!
[Rurino]
Very very thank you! You’re welcome!
Shouldn’t I be the one saying that…?
[Sayaka]
A-Anyway, we should decide who goes first–
Have fun, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
Right, Acting Leader?
…Somehow I knew this would happen!
[Sayaka]
Hello, everyone.
I am Murano Sayaka, a first-year in the Hasunosora School Idol Club.
[Sayaka]
Today, I have some announcements regarding our
performance in our school’s upcoming Rindou Festival.
[Sayaka]
Sayaka-chaaan, don’t forget to smile!
[Kaho]
O-Okay…!
[Sayaka]
With the addition of Mira-Cra Park!,
our upcoming performance will have all three subunits performing in it, so we hope to see you all there.
[Sayaka]
Of note in this performance is the opportunity to unveil our full, six-member School Idol Club–
And of course, our motivation as we look toward the upcoming Love Live! qualifiers.
[Sayaka]
As a school idol myself, I am looking forward to performing in the competition!
How was that, I wonder…
[Sayaka]
I don’t think I said anything wrong, but…
Aaand cut!
[Kaho]
The way you said everything so neatly was really cool, Sayaka-chan!
I think that was great!
[Kaho]
P-Phew…
[Sayaka]
Okay, let’s switch places now.
Hi everyone! I’m Hinoshita Kaho, a first-year from the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
[Kaho]
Hi e-very-one~?
Huh, you want me to respond!?
[Sayaka]
G-Good afternoon…
Yeah, ‘afternoon!
[Kaho]
All of us are really working hard with our Rindou Festival coming up, buuut!
Now that I’ve been a school idol for half a year, it’s time to take on Love Live!
[Kaho]
I hear there’s a looot of school idols that are gonna be competing in the qualifiers, so…
Since we’re gonna be one of those groups, we’re gonna have to show off what makes us so charming!
[Kaho]
Looks like this is gonna be very, very hard!
But that’s exactly why I wanna blossom!
[Kaho]
The Rindou Festival we’ll be using as our stage is an important tradition here at Hasunosora, so we wanna do as much as we can!
We hope you’ll come and support us!
[Kaho]
…How was that?
I thought it was amazing!
[Sayaka]
That’s right…
While we are using it for our Love Live! entry, the Rindou Festival is still an important tradition…
[Sayaka]
Yay!
[Kaho]
So you’re the only one left, Rurino-chan. Think you can do it?
Wow…
[Rurino]
All I could think of was how cool you two were…
I couldn’t think of anything for the video, but I’m feeling more encouraged now!
[Rurino]
There’s no need to worry, Rurino-san.
[Sayaka]
We can re-record as many times as we have to.
I guess so!
[Rurino]
Alright, let’s give it a shot!
If I mess up, we can just do it over!
[Rurino]
She’s motivated, but not in a good way!
[Kaho]
Ah… um…
[Rurino]
I’m School Idol– wait no!
I’m Osawa Rurino, a first-year in the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
[Rurino]
…And… uh…
Shoot, I’m not bad with words or anything, but I’m drawing a blank right now!
[Rurino]
You’ve got this~!
[Kaho]
Hang in there!
[Sayaka]
A-Ahaha, okay, okay!
[Rurino]
Right, Kaho-chan and Sayaka-chan are here for me!
I’ve just gotta act natural and say my thoughts about the Rindou Festival!
[Rurino]
Cogito, ergo Ruri.
Yeah.
[Rurino]
I can’t really say anything special to promote ourselves, but hm…
Mira-Cra Park! will definitely be performing on stage!
[Rurino]
We’ll definitely get that permission!
And… I’m gonna help Megu-chan get her revenge!
[Rurino]
And… about the Love Live! qualifiers, huh…
To be honest, I still don’t get the whole school idol thing.
[Rurino]
I still don’t really know how I’m supposed to feel about competing in Love Live!, either…
Hm…
[Rurino]
…Sorry, all I could think about has to do with Megu-chan.
I probably don’t even know one percent of the fun that goes into being a school idol.
[Rurino]
We probably ought to cut this out and re-record–
…Oh, I see.
[Rurino]
Rurino-san?
[Sayaka]
I-I think I figured it out!
[Rurino]
That time I watched Megu-chan editing videos, I remember I wanted to give it a go!
So it’s like…
[Rurino]
I really like fun stuff!
When I was thinking how I’d want to tweak the video, I was really excited to see how much fun it’d be!
[Rurino]
I guess school idols are kinda like that!
Maybe it’s not good for me to have Megu-chan as my only reason, but I can’t lie to myself!
[Rurino]
I wanna be there for Megu-chan’s revenge!
Right now, whenever I see the fun stuff Megu-chan does, it makes me wanna try a bunch of stuff out too!
[Rurino]
That’s how I feel about Love Live!
If it’ll be fun, then I’m gonna do it!
[Rurino]
That’s how I’ve always done things!
And that’s exactly why I wanna perform in Love Live!
[Rurino]
Perfeeeect!
[Kaho]
Whoa, really!?
[Rurino]
That was really good!
[Kaho]
You’ll do it because it seems fun…
[Sayaka]
You said the same thing back when you first joined the club, right?
Oh! Yeah, yeah, I did!
[Rurino]
Looks like that still hasn’t changed!
Hehe, seems so.
[Sayaka]
I think that’s a very charming part of you.
You’re doing it because it seems fun!
[Kaho]
Let’s rub it in that student council president’s face!
Aw, yeah!
[Rurino]
Hehe, maybe I’ll pull a Megu-chan and throw a lil’ edit together…!
I don’t think Megumi-senpai edits like that, though…
[Sayaka]
Besides, is that really something you can learn just by watching her!?
[Kaho]