Whoa, so many people…
[Rurino]
I’d rather come in just before class starts in the morning. Everyone’s so motivated…
Oh, right, you weren’t around back during the Nadeshiko Festival, huh?
[Kaho]
At our school, everyone gets super motivated when it’s time to prepare for the school festivals!
I’m sorry you two had to be dragged along for this.
[Sayaka]
Don’t worry about it!
[Rurino]
It’s just a simple errand, so it’s kinda like going for a nice walk!
You only need to give them this one paper to get permission to use the stage at the festival, right?
[Kaho]
They don’t need anything else, right?
Yes, this should be everything.
[Sayaka]
The committee person told me that all I had to do was just submit this here.
Coming through!
[Kaho]
Gah… can’t see…!
[Rurino]
‘Scuse me!
Alright, approved.
[Sachi]
The wind ensemble will be allowed to use the stage.
The choir, too.
[Sachi]
Oh, it’s Kaho-chan!
[Shiina]
And she’s with some other people from the School Idol Club!
Oh hi, Shiina-chan! Hi, you three!
[Kaho]
Oh, does the choir need something from the student council too?
Yeah.
[Biwako]
It’d be pretty rough if we couldn’t use the stage…
They didn’t make you do anything weird, right?
[Rurino]
Something like, you need to defeat the student council president to use it!?
Ahaha, nah, nothing crazy like that.
[Ena]
We hope you guys enjoy the festival!
Thank you very much, everyone.
[Sayaka]
We should head in as well.
Next? Come in.
[Sachi]
Excuse us!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Rurino]
Ooh…
[Sachi]
Well, if it isn’t you!
Yes, we’re from the School Idol Club!
[Kaho]
What’s up!?
[Rurino]
Yeah, what’s up~?
[Sachi]
The sky!
[Kaho]
G-Good afternoon…
[Sayaka]
Hahaha, what are you here for?
[Sachi]
The first-years going directly to the student council… What, you planning a mutiny?
M-Mutiny!?
[Kaho]
I don’t know what that means, so I’ll go with “yes!”
[Rurino]
No, that’s not what we’re here for!
[Sayaka]
We’re not trying to betray the second years.
‘Kay, ‘kay. Good to hear it.
[Sachi]
Lay it on me, then.
You’re up, Leader!
[Rurino]
We’re counting on you!
[Kaho]
Hm?
[Sachi]
U-Um…
[Sayaka]
We wanted to request permission to use the stage.
I have the necessary form filled out right here.
[Sayaka]
…Doesn’t it feel like she’s about to say no…?
[Rurino]
W-Well…
[Sayaka]
Megumi-senpai did tell us it’d be fine, so…
Nah, it should be fine.
[Kaho]
Ena-chan said so, right?
She said that there weren’t any crazy conditions to it.
[Kaho]
By the way…
[Sachi]
Y-Yes!
[Sayaka]
Where’s Kozue?
[Sachi]
I was expecting her to come bring this.
Oh, well…
[Kaho]
the thing is, she actually caught a cold…
Right now, our Acting Leader’s giving it everything she’s got!
[Rurino]
A-Acting Leader here!
[Sayaka]
I see. I see…
[Sachi]
It says here that you’re planning on livestreaming your performance.
You planning on using your Rindou Festival performance for the Love Live! qualifiers?
[Sachi]
Yes, that’s our plan.
[Sayaka]
So you are going for Love Live! I see…
[Sachi]
Are you gonna tell us to “Concentrate on the Rindou Festival!” or something?
[Rurino]
Nah, nah, I already know why you need the festival.  The energy there synergizes with your goals.
[Sachi]
So if you’re gonna qualify for Love Live!, you’re gonna need a good performance at the Rindou Festival, right?
Y-Yeah, that’s right!
[Rurino]
Megu-chan wants to qualify this year, so she’s really fired up!
Super burning…? Hot?
[Rurino]
Something like that!
…Yeah, that tracks.
[Sachi]
Kozue-senpai said she’ll definitely get better before the festival!
[Kaho]
…Yep.
[Sachi]
I also want to do everything I can.
[Sayaka]
I know that Tsuzuri-senpai has a lot of thoughts about what happened here last year…
…I see. I see…
[Sachi]
Kaho, Sayaka, and Rurino… right?
Y-Yes!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Rurino]
Why do you three wanna perform at Love Live!?
[Sachi]
Huh? Why…?
[Sayaka]
Why indeed…?
I mean, Megu-chan was really fired up for it.
[Rurino]
Because Love Live! is Kozue-senpai’s dream!
[Kaho]
Hm… I see.
[Sachi]
So that’s the way it is, huh?
And those three…
[Sachi]
Alright! Get out there!
Oh, nice! We got permission!
[Rurino]
No? There’s no way I can accept this the way things are now!
[Sachi]
What!?
[Kaho & Sayaka & Rurino]
What I meant by “get out there” was…
[Sachi]
get out there and pass these three tests!
Why is it just the School Idol Club that has to go through this!?
[Rurino]
We have to hand out all of these…
[Kaho]
But the choir didn’t have to deal with this!
[Rurino]
This is oppression!
Spreading the word about the Rindou Festival with people outside the school…
[Sayaka]
I guess that is pretty important…
But that isn’t a test! That’s just unpaid labor!
[Rurino]
I know her game!
Grr…
[Kaho]
And to think that student council president used to be a school idol!
Huh? I didn’t know that!
[Rurino]
Wait, does she think she can boss us around because she used to be a part of us!?
…I don’t think so.
[Sayaka]
I’m sure she has some purpose in doing all of this.
If she didn’t, she probably would have just outright refused our request.
[Sayaka]
So, what’s this “purpose” then?
[Rurino]
That…
[Sayaka]
I don’t know.
Mmm…
[Kaho]
Fine!!
Kaho-san?
[Sayaka]
It makes sense when you put it like that!
[Kaho]
Let’s take on that student council president’s tests!
Wait… seriously?
[Rurino]
I’m serious! Super serious! Giga serious!
[Kaho]
After all, if we don’t get this permission, there’s no way I could show my face to Kozue-senpai ever again!
That makes sense.
[Rurino]
At least some of it did.
Some of it.
[Kaho]
There’s no way I’d let Megu-chan not get her revenge!
[Rurino]
Thank you very much, you two.
[Sayaka]
…Alright, let’s go!
Yeah, leave it to me!!
[Kaho]
If all we need to do is hand out these flyers, then I’ve got a great plan!
A great plan?
[Sayaka & Rurino]