Huh!? You’re finished already!?
[Sachi]
Yes!
[Kaho & Sayaka]
…And that is…?
[Sachi]
Don’t worry about me.
[Rurino]
O-Okay…
[Sachi]
But seriously, I’m impressed.
I expected that to take like three days or something.
[Sachi]
Wait, you’re telling us we could’ve taken three days!?
[Kaho]
No way! After we worked ourselves that hard!?
[Sayaka]
Ahaha!
[Sachi]
True, I didn’t tell you how much time you had to do it.
My bad, that’s on me.
[Sachi]
Alright, then…
Excuse me!
[Kaho]
I was just wondering, are these tests for–
Hm, I wonder…
[Sachi]
Maybe I just felt like bothering you.
Or maybe I really felt like bothering you.
[Sachi]
Perhaps I felt like bothering you.
Aren’t all three of those options the same!?
[Sayaka]
Ahahaha!
[Sachi]
As much as I’d love to keep looking at those bewildered looks you three have, I’ll give you your second test tomorrow!
We’re done here for today!
[Sachi]
I’m really busy, so get outta here!
And now you’re kicking us out!?
[Kaho]
Alright, fine, I’ll give you a trolley to help you carry that box out.
[Sachi]
And I guess you can take some sweets as a souvenir.
It’s just on top of these shelves.
[Sachi]
…You mind if I use that box as a stepstool?
There’s someone in there, you know!
[Sayaka]
So basically, she dodged the question.
[Megumi]
It didn’t seem like she was planning on telling us the answer when we asked, either.
[Sayaka]
I see…
[Megumi]
I’ll be right back.
[Tsuzuri]
Hold it, hold it!
[Megumi]
I feel like I already know the answer, but where are you going?
…To ask her to not get in our way.
[Tsuzuri]
I kinda expected that.
[Megumi]
Listen, even if you did go to the student council room, there’s no way anyone would be there this late.
…Her room, then.
[Tsuzuri]
You’re really gonna go to her room, Tsuzuri?
[Megumi]
U-Um…
[Kaho]
How was Kozue-senpai feeling today?
Well, it’s been so up and down with her!
[Megumi]
Every time her fever goes down even a little, she’s all like,
“Alright, I should be good enough for practice!”
[Megumi]
I ought to tie her to her bed!
Oh, no…
[Kaho]
I hope she gets better in time.
[Tsuzuri]
Yeah. I couldn’t imagine performing without her.
[Megumi]
…Megu-chan.
[Rurino]
Hm?
[Megumi]
I’m sorry for all of this, Megu-chan.
[Rurino]
Huh?
[Megumi]
By all of this, do you mean not getting permission to use the stage?
Yeah…
[Rurino]
…What could that girl be thinking…?
[Megumi]
I don’t have a clue.
It was like this even back then.
[Megumi]
…Are you talking about the time when she was still in the School Idol Club?
[Kaho]
Yeah.
[Megumi]
I guess she really helped us out?
And I’m grateful that she took care of us?
[Megumi]
I get that she had her own situation, but…
sometimes I had no idea how she felt about anything.
[Megumi]
And she’d make suggestions like, “Wouldn’t it be better like this?” that I didn’t understand.
Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
Well, a lot of stuff happened.
[Megumi]
A lot.
…I get that.
[Rurino]
This is your second shot at the Love Live! qualifiers, Megu-chan!
I won’t let her get in the way of that!
[Rurino]
Y-Yeah, I agree!
[Kaho]
We’ll definitely pry that permission out of her!
Heh, yeah!
[Megumi]
Kozue’s also working hard to recover, so it looks like all of us are real busy~☆
Remind me, what was our goal?
[Megumi]
Tell me, Acting Leader Sayaka-san!
For all of us… to qualify.
[Sayaka]
That’s right.
[Megumi]
So you’ve gotta really do your best, Sayaka-chan!
Right…
[Sayaka]
and as for what tests the student council president has in store for us,
I think I can probably answer them.
[Sayaka]
Seriously!? It’s just me, then!?
[Rurino]
I’m gonna end up holding Megu-chan back!
Ah, no! I’m not totally sure if I’m right, either!
[Sayaka]
Waaah!
[Rurino]
Help, I don’t want to be baggage!
You spent half the day in a box.
[Megumi]
You know that’s not what I meant!
[Rurino]
Of course we’ll work together, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Ooh…
[Rurino]
Friends really are the most important things in life…
Oh, these sweets…
[Megumi]
Ah, right.
[Sayaka]
The president gave them to us as a souvenir earlier.
Hmm…
[Megumi]
Hmph…
This flavor pisses me off.
[Megumi]