And… there.
[Sachi]
To think Kozue of all people would catch a cold…
That’s not something you see often.
[Sachi]
…There’s a pretty good chance you’ll feel better by the Rindou Festival, but…
Get well soon.
[Sachi]
Everyone’s waiting for you.
But still…
[Sachi]
all of them really said that they were doing this “for the second-years,” huh…
They must really love you three.
[Sachi]
You found yourself some real nice girls, you know.
I thought I did pretty well with the three I got, but…
[Sachi]
Not bad, Kozue. Not bad.
…I can’t wait to see you win Love Live!, Kozue.
[Sachi]
….Sachi…senpai…?
[Kozue]
Oh, you awake?
[Megumi]
Megumi…
[Kozue]
What time is it?
Around 4:00 in the afternoon.
[Megumi]
But anyway…
Did you have a dream about someone?
[Tsuzuri]
…Did Sachi-senpai come over?
[Kozue]
I dunno.
[Tsuzuri]
I swear, that girl’s just like a cat.
[Megumi]
She might’ve decided to come over, but I have no idea.
…I see.
[Kozue]
Speaking of Sachi-senpai, it looks like she’s been messing with the first-years.
[Megumi]
She gave them “tests,”
and she’s been making them do all sorts of things.
[Megumi]
I figured I’d just wait and see what happens, but what do you think, Kozue?
I… see.
[Kozue]
Personally, I–
Is it really okay leaving it to her?
[Tsuzuri]
Where is she!?
[Rurino]
We went through the trouble of rushing here and she’s not home!?
[Kaho]
N-No, I don’t think she actually lives here…
[Sayaka]
Oh, you’re already here?
[Sachi]
That was quick.
Ah, there you are, student council president!
Just where were you? Geez!
[Kaho]
Huh…?
[Sachi]
I had a lot of stuff to do in the schoolyard…
so I’m sorry…?
[Sachi]
It is what it is, so I’ll let it slide this time, I guess!
[Rurino]
Thanks…?
[Sachi]
I don’t think you actually need to apologize for that…
[Sayaka]
I was just wondering, what’s that tablet in your hands for?
[Kaho]
Oh, this?
[Sachi]
It’s for preparing the stage for the festival.
See?
[Sachi]
What is any of this supposed to mean…
[Rurino]
Ahahaha! It’d be pretty rough if you didn’t like this kinda thing, huh!
[Sachi]
Wait, does that mean you…?
[Sayaka]
Well, yeah.
[Sachi]
Creating the stage, decorating the location, and preparing everything based on what whoever’s using it wants…
Guess I really like stuff like that.
[Sachi]
Though I am still taking that stage away from your club.
You actually admit it!?
[Kaho]
So you really are planning on taking it away from us!
[Rurino]
Ahaha!
[Sachi]
Now, if you want me to return that stage to you–
wait, if you’re here, then that means…?
[Sachi]
Yes, we’ve completed your second test…
[Sayaka]
I think.
That means you’ve uploaded the video, then?
[Sachi]
Oh, you can sit down.
I got sweets for you.
[Sachi]
Oh, and I had a box prepared, just for you.
Yaaay.
[Rurino]
Are you really okay with that…?
[Sayaka]
I was feelin’ pretty tired, actually–
[Rurino]
This should be good.
I feel like we’re so used to it now…
[Kaho]
To a talking box…
Hehehe…
[Sachi]
‘Kay, I’m gonna watch your video now.
Take it easy for a bit.
[Sachi]
Okay.
[Kaho & Sayaka]
Do you like this brand?
[Kaho]
Kinda, yeah.
[Sachi]
But it’s not just me, your second-years like it, too.
It was actually one of Tsuzuri’s favorites.
[Sachi]
She’s the one that told me about it.
Huh?
[Sayaka]
Hm?
[Sachi]
Wait, did I say something just now?
Ah, no. It was just that part about Tsuzuri-senpai liking these sweets.
[Sayaka]
Oh…
[Sachi]
Um…
[Kaho]
Alright, I’m done watching your video!
[Sachi]
Time to announce the results of your second test!
You’re just trying to change the subject, aren’t you!?
[Sayaka]
Ahaha!
[Sachi]
As you know, the second test was to make a video advertising your club!
Seeing as you made it, you’ve passed!
[Sachi]
And the actual video was good, too!
T-Thank you very much.
[Sayaka]
Kaho, I like how you got directly to the point.
[Sachi]
You want to blossom.
Yeah, I think that’s perfect!
[Sachi]
Y-Yeah!
[Kaho]
You too, Rurino.
[Sachi]
Because it’s fun, huh?
It’s clear that as a first-year, you’re going to keep having fun as a school idol.
[Sachi]
That’s also very good!
Open!
[Rurino]
Phew. Yay!
Ah, you’re fully recharged now?
[Sayaka]
That was really comfy!
[Rurino]
Hm.
[Sachi]
Looks like I found a really good box.
What even makes a good box?
[Kaho]
Now, Sayaka.
[Sachi]
Y-Yes?
[Sayaka]
–There’s a lot of school idols that don’t compete in Love Live!, you know?
[Sachi]
…Huh?
[Sayaka]
Love Live! isn’t the only thing school idols exist for.
[Sachi]
Of course, a lot of school idols share the goal of appearing in Love Live!,
but it’s not as if they have no choice but to.
[Sachi]
It’s not simply a matter of being competitors.
Um. So that means…?
[Kaho]
Sayaka.
[Sachi]
Why is Love Live!--
No, let me rephrase.
[Sachi]
Why do you want to be a school idol?
What’s your reason?
[Sachi]
I…
[Sayaka]
Kaho and Rurino pass.
[Sachi]
Honestly, they don’t even have to take the third test.
Huh?
[Kaho & Rurino]
Sayaka, I’m giving you your third test!
[Sachi]
–Why did you become a school idol?
Give me your answer.
[Sachi]