As a school idol myself, I am looking forward to performing in the competition!
[Sayaka]
…It isn’t a given that we have to compete…
Why I became a school idol…
[Sayaka]
There’s a ton of reasons to become a school idol, aren’t there!?
[Kaho]
Kaho-san…
[Sayaka]
A ton…
[Rurino]
a ton, huh…
Huh, Rurino-chan!?
[Kaho]
No, it’s just… The reason I became a school idol is because it looked interesting?
[Rurino]
And just that?
And I still passed?
[Rurino]
Mine was pretty silly, so I was just wondering why yours wasn’t okay, Sayaka-chan.
I… hm, I wonder…
[Kaho]
I think… I understand.
[Sayaka]
Huh?
[Kaho & Rurino]
–I don’t have a reason for becoming a school idol.
[Sayaka]
N-No, that’s not true!
[Kaho]
No way, no way! Where’d you get that from!?
[Rurino]
I mean, there’s no reason for you not to–
[Kaho]
I know that there’s no reason for me not to! I get that!
[Sayaka]
I get it, but…
I wanted to perform in Love Live! because I wanted to do my best together with everyone.
[Sayaka]
I thought that since there was a school idol competition, it would only be natural to perform in it.
If you told me that all I need to express myself is my figure skating…
[Sayaka]
I don’t think I would have it in me to say so in return.
That’s not… true, right?
[Rurino]
Even after all this time, thinking that I could act as the leader with everyone’s help…
[Sayaka]
…I’m so frustrated at how shameful I am.
Without a reason to, I have no right to continue.
[Sayaka]
I know that isn’t what she’s trying to say, but…
But is this really the way I feel about being a school idol…?
[Sayaka]
If it weren’t for Tsuzuri-senpai, I wouldn’t have done this.
But now, I have everyone…
[Sayaka]
wait, I’m still using everyone as an excuse, even here…
–Sayaka-san.
[Kozue]
Huh? O-Oh, Kozue-senpai.
[Sayaka]
Are you already feeling better?
Yes, I’d say so.
[Kozue]
I had to use every method I could to recover…!
Are you sure you’re okay!?
[Sayaka]
Hmhm, yes, I’m sure.
[Kozue]
Besides, I couldn’t keep avoiding my club president duties forever.
Ah…
[Sayaka]
I’m sorry…
I couldn’t… do anything…
[Sayaka]
What are you saying?
[Kozue]
The only reason things were able to get done in my absence was your hard work, wasn’t it?
Everyone is grateful to you as well.
[Kozue]
But…
[Sayaka]
you’ve already recovered from your illness, and we still haven’t secured permission for the stage…
I heard there were tests, yes?
[Kozue]
Goodness…
that student council president is such a troublemaker.
[Kozue]
Making things this difficult for our hard-working juniors…
No…
[Sayaka]
This isn’t a problem with the student council president, it has to do with me…
…I thought performing in Love Live! would be the most easily understandable reason for being a school idol, Sayaka-san.
[Kozue]
Ah…
[Sayaka]
so you know about that.
I always assumed that school idols were meant to perform in Love Live!
[Sayaka]
As a competitor myself, it only seemed natural to want to be a part of such a competition.
But…
[Sayaka]
it isn’t necessary for school idols to perform in Love Live!
And besides, all my reasons for continuing to be a school idol have been solely for other people…
[Sayaka]
I see.
[Kozue]
Kozue-senpai…
[Sayaka]
I don’t know what I should do…
Do you?
[Sayaka]
…I do.
[Kozue]
That isn’t something I can answer, though.
So it’s something I have to think of for myself…
[Sayaka]
That’s true, but to put it more bluntly…
[Kozue]
If I were to answer, you would think you were simply borrowing my words, wouldn’t you?
I think that ultimately, this is an answer everyone needs to find for themselves.
[Kozue]
But you know, Sayaka-san?
Yes…
[Sayaka]
This is what I think.
[Kozue]
I think you’ve already found your answer.
So, good luck.
[Kozue]
…And perhaps I should take the president work from here.
Huh?
[Sayaka]
Oh… It’s okay, at least let me see this through to the end.
Okay.
[Kozue]
Right… I’m sure you’ll definitely find it… your reason for continuing to be a school idol.
Is this okay here?
[Ena]
I’ve got it!
[Biwako]
Could you raise it for me, please?
Alright! Let’s go ahead and build that there!
[Sachi]
…Even with Kozue-senpai’s hint, I still don’t get it.
[Sayaka]
What does she mean, “I’ve already found it”…?
I think it was a good thing I became a school idol.
[Sayaka]
I think so for a lot of reasons.
But…
[Sayaka]
if it’s because Tsuzuri-senpai recognizes me as one,
or because Kaho-san and Rurino-san support me…
[Sayaka]
then those are just more reasons from other people…
…Oh, isn’t that Sayaka-chan?
[Ena]
Oh, it really is.
[Biwako]
–Heeey! Sayaka-chaaan!
G-Good afternoon.
[Sayaka]
Ahaha, I can’t hear youuu!
[Biwako]
But we did see her bowing.
[Shiina]
Sayaka-chaaan!
[Ena]
Good luck with the Rindou Festivaaal!
We’re rooting for youuu!
[Ena]
Y-Yes!
[Sayaka]
Of course I want to perform…
We have heavy expectations for youuu!!
[Biwako]
Looking forward to iiit!!!
[Shiina]
Of course! I’ll do my very best!!
[Sayaka]
Because I want to meet all your expectations!!
Yeah!
[Ena & Biwako & Shiina]
Phew…
[Sayaka]
We’ll have to do our best too, huh~
[Biwako]
The School Idol Club will just end up poaching all our future club members again if we don’t.
[Ena]
Let’s practice then~
[Shiina]
…I have to do this for that–
[Sayaka]
…Huh? Just now, I…
…Is that it?
[Sayaka]
Maybe this isn’t it.
But–
[Sayaka]
If it is, then it would be incredible.
I– I want to meet everyone’s expectations.
[Sayaka]
Please give us permission to use the stage.
That means you have your answer, yeah?
[Sachi]
I… want to meet everyone’s expectations.
[Sayaka]
And to do so, I want to perform.
I don’t think I could explain it in just words.
[Sayaka]
…Hm.
[Sachi]
Well, at the very least, it doesn’t seem like you’re saying that just so you can get your permission.
No, of course not!
[Sayaka]
Yeah, you don’t seem like that type of person.
[Sachi]
But, a performance, huh?
To meet everyone’s expectations…
[Sachi]
I don’t think you can do that with just your average performance, though.
You aren’t just pushing your reason onto Tsuzuri, or your other club members, or the people supporting you, are you?
[Sachi]
I understand where you’re coming from.
[Sayaka]
President!
Please come to our performance.
[Sayaka]
I’ll definitely show you there.
Through…
[Sayaka]
my solo song.