…Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
I didn’t know anything about her this whole time..
Yet I still had the nerve to act like she was my best friend…
[Rurino]
Is it really too late now…?
Was this… all for nothing…?
[Rurino]
For the love of…
[Kozue]
why would she change so suddenly…?
Right?
[Tsuzuri]
Kozue-senpai, Tsuzuri-senpai…
[Rurino]
Ah, Rurino-san.
[Kozue]
Megumi just dropped by and told us to get rid of her stuff.
We ended up having to go all the way to the warehouse as a result.
[Kozue]
Does that mean…
[Rurino]
Megu-chan won’t be coming back to the School Idol Club…?
Possibly…
[Kozue]
It’s all my fault…
[Rurino]
All because I pushed her too hard…
…I guess something did happen.
[Kozue]
Huh…?
[Rurino]
Those shoes…!
Huh?
[Kozue & Tsuzuri]
I never noticed…
[Rurino]
Those are the shoes I gave Megu-chan.
They’re different sizes, but they’re all the same kind…
[Rurino]
They’re so worn out…
She must’ve practiced so much in these…
[Rurino]
I never knew…
Megumi was the hardest worker I knew.
[Kozue]
You know, I asked her once.
[Tsuzuri]
I wondered why she kept all these shoes.
…And what did she say?
[Kozue]
She said…
[Tsuzuri]
Every time I look at these shoes, I think to myself,
[Megumi]
I’ve run really far, haven’t I?
And if there was a girl out there that could catch up to me…
[Megumi]
Then I’d have no choice but to make an unbeatable unit with her to captivate the whole world, right?
I-I’ve gotta go!
[Rurino]
Huh? Where–
[Tsuzuri]
And she’s gone.
…You really have quite the memory.
[Kozue]
It was…
[Tsuzuri]
a lot of fun.
Of course I remember.
[Tsuzuri]
Megu-chan! Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Huh? R-Ruri-chan…?
[Megumi]
W-What is it?
Listen! I finally figured it out!
[Rurino]
About you! And about me!
H-Huh? About what…?
[Megumi]
I didn’t come to like you because you were so cool, or because you could do anything.
[Rurino]
I like you because you’re you, Megu-chan!
I’ve always thought that way!
[Rurino]
W-Wait, you’re gonna bother people…
[Megumi]
ugh, fine, just get inside!
Oh… those shoes…
[Rurino]
you have them here, too…
These are just…!
[Megumi]
I-I only use them to go running sometimes!
Like when I go for a breather and stuff!
[Megumi]
And I figured I’d keep buying the shoes I’m used to wearing…
…Megu-chan.
[Rurino]
I’m sorry for not noticing how hard you’ve been working this whole time.
N-No…
[Megumi]
I shouldn’t have lied to you in the first place.
You always shone the way forward for me.
[Rurino]
And yet, I only made things harder for you…
I’m sorry.
[Rurino]
…Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
Thanks for everything.
[Rurino]
But I’ll be okay now!
Huh…?
[Megumi]
This time, I’ll be the one guiding you forward!
[Rurino]
I’m way stronger than I was back then!
I spent two years in California, a place filled with people I didn’t know, all by myself!
[Rurino]
And just like we promised, I got big and came back!
Maybe you don’t think I’m ready yet, but I mean it!
[Rurino]
I’ll be okay!
I’ve gotten waaay stronger, and I’m gonna prove it to you!
[Rurino]
I’ll show you a new Ruri!
So let’s do it!
[Rurino]
Let’s be school idols, together!
What’s done is done!
[Rurino]
The past is in the past!
From now on, I’ll pull you forward, and you’ll pull me forward too!
[Rurino]
We’ll be a new MeguRuri!
We can start fresh, right here!
[Rurino]
I’ll be waiting, Megu-chan!
Ruri-chan…
[Megumi]
I… I…
Ruri-chan…
[Megumi]
I…
I…!
[Megumi]
No matter how many times I stumble and fall, the only thing I can’t do is give up!
Because…
[Megumi]
Because you’re waiting for me!
Ah…
[Rurino]
A-Ahaha…
Performing by myself is pretty tough…
[Rurino]
But it’s kinda sad that I’m like this after trying to act so cool earlier, y’know…
That’s not true.
[Megumi]
You were cool, Ruri-chan.
Very, very cool.
[Megumi]
Ahaha, thanks…
[Rurino]
Megu-chan, thanks for coming!
No, no.
[Megumi]
The one who came for me was you, Ruri-chan.
S-stop it, you’re gonna make me cry up on stage!
[Rurino]
Hehehe.
[Megumi]
Okay then, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Let’s do this together!
Yeah, Ruri-chan!
[Megumi]
The two of us will captivate the whole world!
Okay, everyone!
[Megumi]
Let’s get fired up today!
I’m gonna do my usual thing, ‘kay~? ☆
[Megumi]
Everyone! HelloMegu!
HelloMegu!
[Crowd]
And, and!
[Rurino]
The two of us are a subunit from the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
And our name is…!
[Megumi]
One, two…!
[Rurino]
Mira-Cra Park!
[Megumi & Rurino]
Gah…
[Rurino]
I’m exhausted…
You did it, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Agh.
[Rurino]
Your performance was a great success!
[Sayaka]
It’s gotta be because of all the energy we sent from offstage!
[Kaho]
T-Time-out!
[Rurino]
My battery’s totally drained right now!
If you cling to me like that, I’ll die! I’m dying!
[Rurino]
Congratulations on making your comeback, Megumi.
[Kozue]
Yeah…
[Megumi]
And sorry for worrying you two so much, Kozue, Tsuzuri.
And…
[Megumi]
I’m back.
…I-It’s not as if I was waiting for you or anything…
[Kozue]
Your stuff is all still in the clubroom, so it’ll be your responsibility to take it back to the warehouse.
Welcome home, Megu.
[Tsuzuri]
…Y-Yeah…
[Megumi]
Ahaha, all this fanfare is a little embarrassing…
Oh? Looks like Megumi-senpai’s getting embarrassed~.
[Kaho]
This side of her is surprisingly cute, huh?
[Sayaka]
H-Hey!
[Megumi]
I’m a year above you two, so you should still respect me, you know! Hmph!
Megu-chan! Good job!
[Rurino]
You really, really worked hard today!
Hm, hm…!
[Megumi]
Yeah…
Hey, Ruri-chan?
[Megumi]
…Sorry for being so stubborn.
Honestly… I’m really, really happy you came here.
[Megumi]
Thank you, from the bottom of my heart.
M-Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
A-Ah-huh!?
So!
[Megumi]
Next time, let’s stand on stage, together, from the very beginning!
…Yeah!
[Rurino]