Okay, one, two, one, two…
[Megumi]
Alright, that’s enough for now.
Hah… hah… hah…
[Rurino]
How was that, Megu-chan…?
Good. You’ve built up a lot of stamina, and your dancing’s gotten really good, Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
Ehehe, I’ve been practicing a lot.
[Rurino]
…Was that because you wanted to be school idols with me?
[Megumi]
Yeah!
[Rurino]
…I see…
[Megumi]
You’ve loved me since we were kids, huh, Ruri-chan?
I’d say the feeling is mutual~!
[Rurino]
You’d run out of battery real quick if I wasn’t around, after all.
[Megumi]
Guh…
[Rurino]
Listen, thanks to my hero’s journey, my battery life is a lot better now!
We’re talking industrial-grade here!
[Rurino]
Hm… I wonder…
[Megumi]
Leave a girl alone for long enough, and she just might overtake you!
[Rurino]
That reminds me, you used to teach me dancing like this back when we were in grade school, huh?
…Hm, did I~?
[Megumi]
Huh!? You forgot!?
[Rurino]
Yeah, yeah, my bad, guess I did.
[Megumi]
Alright, let’s take a short break here. You should go and rehydrate.
Geez…!
[Rurino]
Fine, I’m going!
Now then.
[Megumi]
What have you two been doing this whole time?
Gulp.
[Kaho & Sayaka]
Were you checking up on me because you were worried I wouldn’t coach her properly?
[Megumi]
We…
[Sayaka]
No, I don’t think there’s anything to criticize from your guidance.
…But we figured that if we left you two alone, you’d just be mean to Rurino-chan like you were before.
[Kaho]
Huh?
[Megumi]
O-Oh, okay…
Hm… Looks like Ruri-chan’s made some good friends here…
[Megumi]
Look, I regret how childish I acted back then, so I’m sorry.
We should just bury the hatchet now, ‘mkaaay~?
[Megumi]
What do you think we should do, Sayaka-chan?
[Kaho]
I don’t mind either way, but…
[Sayaka]
I worry that if things stay strained between us, Rurino-san would be bothered by it.
Mmm…
[Kaho]
I guess so…
Oh, Kaho-chan, Sayaka-chan! What’s up?
[Rurino]
Huh!?
[Kaho]
Uh, we were just here to talk with Megumi-senpai!
Right, right! Exactly that!
[Sayaka]
…Aren’t you a little far from her?
[Rurino]
S-So, Megumi-senpai, we’d really appreciate it if you could coach me too some time~♪
[Kaho]
Me, too! If you could, I’d really, really appreciate it!
[Sayaka]
Okay~♪ You know I can’t say no to my cute juniors~!
[Megumi]
T-This is just for Rurino-chan, okay…!
[Kaho]
Okay, sure.
[Megumi]
Let’s go with that, then.
You’ve gotten this close already…!?
[Rurino]
What can I say, I’m a natural~☆
[Megumi]
…Megumi-senpai, you used to be school idols together with Kozue-senpai and Tsuzuri-senpai, right?
[Kaho]
Yeah, we were.
[Megumi]
You know, the three of us…
They used to call us the Hasu Big Three because we were the shining beacons of hope in the School Idol Club.
[Megumi]
Hasu Big Three!?
[Kaho]
So cool!
[Rurino]
…You know they used to call us the Problem Children too.
[Kozue]
Hmph.
[Megumi]
Yeah, I remember…
[Tsuzuri]
You two were a real handful.
You don’t get to say that!
You’re one to talk!
You’re the one that used to argue with our senior so much, Kozue!
[Megumi]
Going on and on about whether “our practice was enough to win Love Live!”...!
Wait, she did!?
[Kaho]
And you caused so much trouble just because you wanted to show off, Megumi.
[Kozue]
What about that time you said, “This song will be way more popular if I were in the center more☆”?
She said that!?
[Rurino]
Look how far these two have come.
[Tsuzuri]
…I suppose.
[Kozue]
You even come to practice on time nowadays, Tsuzuri.
She does!?
[Megumi]
Peace.
[Tsuzuri]
It’s thanks to Saya.
I am so, so grateful you have self-awareness…
[Kozue]
Normally, this would be the time to say, “Oh no, I didn’t do anything!” but...
[Sayaka]
No worries, Sayaka-san.
[Kozue]
There’s no need to lie to cover for your seniors.
Then why don’t we make Saya one of the seniors?
[Tsuzuri]
What are you suggesting!?
[Sayaka]
Saya-senpai.
[Tsuzuri]
No, stop!
[Sayaka]
My self-confidence would be shattered if I saw a junior dance as well as you!
Saya-senpaaaai.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s enough, Tsuzuri-chan!
[Sayaka]
Wait, no!
You two certainly are close…
[Kozue]
You know that applies to you as well, right~?
[Megumi]
What does?
[Kozue]
You know, back when I went to visit after you fell from the stage while rehearsing for the Kanazawa performance?
[Megumi]
You spent that whole time crying and calling out, “Kaho-san, Kaho-san…”
I was not crying!
[Kozue]
I knew from the very beginning.
[Megumi]
You’re strict with your seniors and those in the same year as you, but you spoil your juniors rotten~.
I don’t do that.
[Kozue]
They think I’m the meanest demon.
Right, Kaho-san?
[Kozue]
She’s still hung up on that…!
[Kaho]
But that was a very difficult time, huh!
I was so worried that I got you really injured, Kozue-senpai.
[Kaho]
On the bright side, it was nothing too
serious, and I was able to protect you.
[Kozue]
Oh, is that why you always tell us to be careful not to get hurt…?
[Kaho]
…That’s right.
[Kozue]
I would hate to lose another friend.
U-Um!
[Kaho]
Are you really not able to dance anymore, Megumi-senpai!?
Kaho-san…
[Sayaka]
Yeah, that’s right.
[Megumi]
But you were able to while you were teaching Rurino-chan, weren’t you?
[Kaho]
Because we weren’t on stage.
[Megumi]
…But… I thought you’d fully recovered…
[Kaho]
I haven’t.
[Megumi]
Well, I might someday, but I don’t know if or when that’ll happen.
…Megumi.
[Kozue]
I had fun being a school idol.
[Megumi]
I have very good memories of that time.
Then even if you can’t dance, you can still be a school idol, can’t you!?
[Kaho]
Kaho-san, that’s enough!
[Sayaka]
But!
[Kaho]
But… it’s so…
Everyone has their own definition of what a school idol is.
[Megumi]
Of course, I think that it’s perfectly fine even if a school idol doesn’t dance.
But that’s not the kind of school idol I aspire to be.
[Megumi]
Kozue, Tsuzuri.
I’m happy you have these three amazing juniors in your club.
[Megumi]
I always worried that the School Idol Club wouldn’t be able to get new members and would have to disband.
If the club were to wither and die out without me, that’d leave me with some big regrets, you know?
[Megumi]
…What are you saying?
[Kozue]
Of course... It wouldn’t...
Yeah.
[Megumi]
It looks like you and Tsuzuri have made up, so that’s great.
I guess I have nothing to worry about anymore.
[Megumi]
I’m…! I’m gonna go for a quick run!
[Rurino]
Huh? Why?
[Megumi]
I.. I haven’t given up yet!
[Rurino]
I’m going! For the plan!
I-I’m going, too!
[Kaho]
We can still keep at it!
I’ll be accompanying them, then!
[Sayaka]
They truly are wonderful juniors.
[Kozue]
…Seems so.
[Megumi]