Nice! You’ve really gotten the steps down, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
If you keep this up, tomorrow’s performance will go great!
[Sayaka]
Ehehe, really!? Yay!
[Rurino]
Well, I am a little worried about running out of battery up there, but I’m sure I’ll manage!
I’m a school idol now, after all!
[Rurino]
Then we’ll stand just offstage and send you our energy!
[Kaho]
Just… like this!
Do it with me, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
Huh!? U-Uh, okay!
[Sayaka]
Good luck, Rurino-chan…
[Kaho]
Good luck, good luck…
I pray you’ll finish strong…!
[Sayaka]
Ahaha, thanks, you two! Thank you!
[Rurino]
Megu-chan.
Ruri-chan, come with me.
[Megumi]
You really shocked Kaho-chan and Sayaka-chan there, y’know?
[Rurino]
I mean, you just came over with this scary look on your face.
I wonder how I’ll explain this to them later~.
[Rurino]
What’s the meaning of this?
[Megumi]
Why did you put my name on this?
You didn’t even–
[Megumi]
Hey, Megu-chan, why don’t you go out there with me?
[Rurino]
Let’s perform together!
…This isn’t a joke.
[Megumi]
I can’t dance anymore because of my injury.
This is just…
[Megumi]
this is just rude, Ruri-chan.
You’re coming with me…
[Rurino]
I’ve already decided, you’re going out there and performing with me!
For the last time, I–!
[Megumi]
You’re coming! I’m not taking no for an answer!
[Rurino]
You’ll be out there with me! We’re doing this together!
It’s not that simple, you know!
[Megumi]
You’re coming!
[Rurino]
Didn’t… Didn’t you want to perform too?
Then let’s just do it! Together!
[Rurino]
I… I’ve…
[Megumi]
I’ve already given up on it.
That still hasn’t changed…
[Megumi]
I’m worried that this might not go well, too, but…
[Rurino]
But as long as I’m with you, I’m sure I can do this!
So please, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
I’ll be waiting!
That’s…
[Megumi]
Ah… Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
It’s been so long!
Yeah, it has.
[Megumi]
How’ve you been since you transferred?
Made any new friends?
[Megumi]
…N-Not really…
[Rurino]
You’re not here, so…
Alright, looks like you need a present from good old Megu-chan then!
[Megumi]
Hey, are you home right now?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
[Rurino]
Could ya turn your TV on?
[Megumi]
Okay…
[Rurino]
Ah! You’re on TV, Megu-chan!
Wow! That’s so amazing! How did this happen!?
[Rurino]
Stuff like this is easy when I get serious~!
[Megumi]
Wow~
[Rurino]
So, Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
That’s enough moping around, got it?
Huh…?
[Rurino]
I’ll always be somewhere where you can see me.
[Megumi]
I’ll keep you focused on me.
So I want you to smile, okay?
[Megumi]
…Um, actually, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
I… I wanted to give you a present too!
Huh?
[Megumi]
Thanks, Ruri-chan.
These shoes are super cute!
[Megumi]
Yeah!
[Rurino]
I’m really happy you like them!
Your dancing was always super cool, so I figured…
[Rurino]
You’d probably want ones that are easy to move around in.
Hey, so, Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
I’ve been slowly making more and more friends too!
I’ve been trying really hard.
[Rurino]
That way, one day, I’ll be able to send smiles to you too, Megu-chan.
Hm, hm…
[Megumi]
But I’m getting further and further ahead, you know?
As long as I’ve got these shoes from you, I feel like I can run to the ends of the earth!
[Megumi]
W-Well…!
[Rurino]
Then, I’ll just have to go hard, too!
I’ll go abroad and get big! Then I can take a plane to catch up to you real quick!
[Rurino]
Yeah.
[Megumi]
And then we can have fun together again!
Yeah!
[Rurino]
Let’s have fun together again, Megu-chan!
I’ll definitely catch up to you!
[Rurino]
Yeah.
[Megumi]
I’ll be waiting!
…Those words.
[Megumi]
Huh?
[Rurino]
No, never mind.
[Megumi]
But, I understand now.
The reason I became a school idol was…
[Megumi]
Because I had so much fun with you.
Experiencing new things together, and seeing everyone around us having so much fun…
[Megumi]
It made me want to captivate them all more and more.
That’s why I’ve been running this long…
[Megumi]
Megu-chan…?
[Rurino]
Sorry, Ruri-chan…
[Megumi]
But you’re too late…
W-Why…?
[Rurino]
I just got back!
It’ll be okay! You were always able to do anything, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Not even an injury could keep you down for long–
No, you’re wrong!
[Megumi]
I’ve been pretending this whole time!
All I was doing was trying to look good for you!
[Megumi]
I would secretly practice dancing all the time!
I failed so many child acting auditions over and over again!
[Megumi]
Huh…?
[Rurino]
All I wanted was for you to be happy…
[Megumi]
for you to keep smiling…
I should’ve told you about my injury much earlier!
[Megumi]
That way, you wouldn’t have felt like you needed to enroll here.
I’ve been running away…
[Megumi]
Because I didn’t want you to see this side of me…
I’m so sorry, Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
Th-that’s…
[Rurino]
You understand now, right, Ruri-chan?
[Megumi]
Fujishima Megumi has never been the cool girl you looked up to.
She’s nothing but a loser and a coward…
[Megumi]
And even now, she’s still terrified of returning to the stage.
I’m so sorry for lying to you all this time.
[Megumi]
M-Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
I’ll always support your school idol activities, okay?
[Megumi]
So… Please take care of the club for me.
Megu-chan…
[Rurino]