You’re so cool, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
You’re so good at dancing!
Just like a grown-up!
[Rurino]
Hehe~, right, riiight?☆
[Megumi]
I only did a little practice at home, you know~☆
Huh!?
[Rurino]
You’re a genius, Megu-chan!
…I actually practiced for three whole days though…
[Megumi]
Huh? Didja say something?
[Rurino]
Oh, nothing! It’s nothing!
[Megumi]
Alright, now it’s your turn, Ruri-chan.
I’m gonna teach you reaaaal good now.
[Megumi]
It’ll be a million times cuter if we dance together!
We’re gonna captivate the whole world, right!?
[Rurino]
Exactly!
[Megumi]
Yaaay!
[Megumi & Rurino]
Huh!?
[Megumi]
You’re changing schools, Ruri-chan!?
…Yeah.
[Rurino]
I don’t want this…
I don’t want to leave you, Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
I want to be with you forever…
Ruri-chan…
[Megumi]
Three days ‘til the performance…
[Rurino]
This time for sure, Megu-chan.
We’ll captivate the whole world…
[Rurino]
I’ve practiced my singing and dancing really hard, and I’ve been doing lots of stamina training!
All that’s left is to get up on stage and work very, very hard… but…
[Rurino]
Haah…
Will I be okay…?
[Rurino]
If my battery dies during the performance, then…
Oh, that’s it.
[Rurino]
‘kay, bye…
R-Ruri-chan…!?
[Megumi]
It’d be a total disaster! Super bad!
[Rurino]
But there’s nothing I could do about it!
Maybe I should install some solar panels on myself!
[Rurino]
Rain, rain, goooo… away!
What are you doing, Ruri-chan?
[Megumi]
M-Making weather charms…
[Rurino]
Okay…
[Megumi]
Well, I guess it makes sense that you’d want good weather when you perform.
Y-Yeah…
[Rurino]
Oh, wait, what are you doing here, Megu-chan?
Could it be that you feel like coming back to the club!?
[Rurino]
Noooope!
[Megumi]
Just here to return the notebook I borrowed from Kozue~.
Huh.
[Rurino]
I guess you’re still not good at studying…
It’s only when it’s for school!
[Megumi]
I just can’t seem to score well on tests.
And that’s why they enrolled you into Hasunosora, huh~
[Rurino]
Yeah! Just when my showbiz career was popping off, too!
[Megumi]
They told me to get a proper education and shipped me off to this dorm!
I thought my life was so over!
[Megumi]
Megu-chan, can you spell “anemone”?
[Rurino]
You think I’m stupid?
[Megumi]
Of course I can…
A- N-… Y-……
[Megumi]
Whatever, it’s too hard!
Ahaha!
[Rurino]
Your performance is coming up pretty soon, right?
[Megumi]
Yeah!
[Rurino]
You’re gonna come watch, right, Megu-chan?
I guess…
[Megumi]
But are you gonna be okay?
Huh, what do you mean?
[Rurino]
Ah, well, I guess I made it seem like I wasn’t ready yet back at the training camp, but still!
I’ve been working on it!
[Rurino]
And also, Kozue-senpai and Tsuzuri-senpai have been super nice!
It was honestly surprising how nice they are!
[Rurino]
Nah, that’s not what I mean.
[Megumi]
I’m talking about how fast you tire out when you’re with other people.
W-Well, I…
[Rurino]
So I was just wondering if you’d actually be able to perform in front of all those people.
[Megumi]
L-Listen! I got a lot of buffs during my time abroad!
[Rurino]
I’m waaay stronger than I was back then!
Really now~.
[Megumi]
But if there’s a chance you might mess up, wouldn’t it be better to get some more practice in?
No problem!
[Rurino]
My special, marvelous performance will definitely make you feel much better, Megu-chan!
About that…
[Megumi]
If you’re really doing this performance for my sake, don’t.
Huh? Why?
[Rurino]
I’m glad you feel that way, and I really am looking forward to seeing you perform, but…
[Megumi]
I’m sorry to say this, but I doubt I’d be able to return to the stage even after that.
Why would you say something like that!?
[Rurino]
It’ll be fine! I’ll be giving it my all!
There are things that even hard work can’t achieve…
[Megumi]
Even back when I stopped contacting you, I did whatever I could to try to come back.
I tried and tried, but in the end, nothing ended up working.
[Megumi]
I tried going to performances from school idols I liked.
I tried helping Kozue and Tsuzuri.
[Megumi]
I tried doing physical therapy.
But nothing changed.
[Megumi]
At this point, I doubt even seeing you perform would…
Are…
[Rurino]
Are you saying all that because you’re worried I might run out of battery during the performance…?
No.
[Megumi]
I just don’t want you to waste your effort on nothing.
But we won’t know if it’ll be a waste until we try!
[Rurino]
Why are you acting this way!?
Is it because you don’t like school idols anymore!?
[Rurino]
Again, no!
[Megumi]
I just want you to be a school idol for yourself, not for me.
I’m sure you’ll have so much fun if you do, so…
[Megumi]
But I want to be a school idol with you!
[Rurino]
You’re so annoying!
[Megumi]
Fine, I’ll just go out and say it, then!
I’m tired of being a school idol!
[Megumi]
I started doing it just to kill time!
There, are you happy now!?
[Megumi]
Is that what you wanted!?
You’re lying!
[Rurino]
I mean, you sounded so happy on the phone…
This time for sure, we’ll be able to captivate the whole world as school idols!
[Megumi]
C’mon, Ruri-chan! Hurry and come to Hasunosora, already–
Stupid Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
No matter what you tell me, I’m not giving up!
Not until…
[Rurino]
not until the two of us are school idols together!
Stupid!
[Rurino]
…Ruri-chan…
[Megumi]
You’re the stupid one…
Why… Why are you doing this much, just for me…?
[Megumi]
Did… something happen?
[Kozue]
Ruri sprinted out of the room just now…
[Tsuzuri]
Megu?
Huh?
[Megumi]
O-Oh, no, it was nothing!
W-We just had a little bit of an argument, but everything’s all… okay…
[Megumi]
Oh, those shoes.
Hm?
[Kozue]
So you still have them in here, huh.
[Megumi]
They’ve been collecting dust for a year now, so you probably should’ve just thrown them away.
…But you haven’t given up on becoming a school idol yet.
[Kozue]
We thought you’d come back someday.
[Tsuzuri]
Yeah…
[Megumi]
yeah.
Kozue… Tsuzuri…
[Megumi]
I… I’m so frustrated…
Ruri-chan said all those things to me, but…
[Megumi]
Whenever I close my eyes, I’m back under those spotlights, and I can’t move…
I tried to dance so many times, but I just couldn’t.
[Megumi]
Even though you two were always there for me, it still didn’t work…
And then I’d ruin the performance, and you’d have to try really hard to cover for me…
[Megumi]
And I know that I should’ve just quit, that I should’ve given up…
All because of these… these worthless…!
[Megumi]
Megumi, you shouldn’t hit your legs like that–
[Kozue]
Especially now that they’re better…
[Tsuzuri]
But!
[Megumi]
But…
I’m always so frustrated…
[Megumi]
Why…? Why can’t I dance on stage anymore…?
What… should I even do…?
[Megumi]
Is there really… no other option for me…?
…Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
I’m gonna do my best.