Thanks, Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
These shoes are super cute!
Hey so, Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
I’ve been slowly making more and more friends too!
I’ve been trying really hard.
[Rurino]
That way, one day, I’ll be able to send smiles to you too, Megu-chan.
Hm, hm…
[Megumi]
But I’m getting further and further ahead, you know?
As long as I’ve got these shoes from you, I feel like I can run to the ends of the earth!
[Megumi]
W-Well…!
[Rurino]
Then, I’ll just have to go hard, too!
I’ll go abroad and get big!
[Rurino]
Then I can take a plane to catch up to you real quick!
Yeah.
[Megumi]
And then we can have fun together again!
Yeah!
[Rurino]
Let’s have fun together again, Megu-chan!
I’ll definitely catch up to you!
[Rurino]
Yeah.
[Megumi]
I’ll be waiting!
HelloMegu!
[Megumi]
Hello to all fifty million soldiers of the Megu Army!
It’s me, Fujishima Megumi!
[Megumi]
How are you all today?
Oh? Did you all miss me~?
[Megumi]
Oh, it’s her!
[Kaho]
She was at the Nadeshiko Festival last year…
[Sayaka]
And she also came to check up on Kozue-senpai when she was in the nurse’s office!
[Kaho]
Megu-chan is my childhood friend.
[Rurino]
She asked me before, actually.
She told me how fun being a school idol was, and that we should do it together.
[Rurino]
But…
[Sayaka]
Yeah…
[Kaho]
I’ve never personally seen her with the club at all.
… You know, she just stopped talking about herself at some point.
[Rurino]
Whenever I’d ask, she’d dodge the question.
I always thought it was kinda weird…
[Rurino]
I didn’t think it was because she wasn’t coming to the club anymore…
What happened, Megu-chan…?
[Rurino]
I’ve been super busy editing videos lately, so I haven’t been able to stream much…
[Megumi]
Sorry~.
But I’ve been keeping all of you in my thoughts.
[Megumi]
I love you all ☆
So when you mentioned going to the second year’s classrooms, Rurino-san…
[Sayaka]
Yeah.
[Rurino]
Well, I didn’t see her, though.
Or maybe she’s avoiding me…
[Rurino]
And then I almost quit the club before I even saw her…
But I’m okay now, because you all accepted me.
[Rurino]
So if she has a reason, I’d like to hear it.
Megu-chan used to always talk about how fun being a school idol is, so...
[Rurino]
Even if I’m a little intimidated to meet with her…
I’m sure I’ll be able to help her!
[Rurino]
And I…
I want to be a school idol together with Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Senpai…
[Kaho]
…You’re right.
[Kozue]
I should tell you about her, Rurino-san.
…Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
Megumi…
[Kozue]
Fujishima Megumi-san will most likely not be returning to the School Idol Club.
Huh…?
[Kaho]
At the Rindo Festival last year, she fell from the stage and suffered an injury.
[Kozue]
And although she has already fully recovered from her injury…
Fully recovered…?
[Sayaka]
I remember hearing that she quit performing because of her injury.
Then why…?
[Rurino]
Megumi is…
[Kozue]
…Ever since then, whenever she would get up on stage, her legs would freeze up.
[Tsuzuri]
She couldn’t dance anymore.
So she stopped being a school idol.
[Tsuzuri]
I… I have to go see her!
[Rurino]
Ah, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
W-We’ll go after her!
[Sayaka]
So this… is Megumi-senpai’s room?
[Kaho]
So you already looked into this, huh, Rurino-san…
[Sayaka]
Megu-chan. Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
Open up, please. It’s Ruri.
Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
Long time no see.
I’m sorry.
[Megumi]
I didn’t come see you even when you came back to the country.
That’s not really a big deal…
[Rurino]
…Why?
Why didn’t you tell me!?
[Rurino]
Why didn’t you say anything about getting injured or not being able to dance anymore!?
We said we’d be school idols together, didn’t we!?
[Rurino]
So why have you been hiding this from me!?
…You’ll bother the other students if you shout in the hallway, Ruri-chan.
[Megumi]
M-Megu-chan…?
[Rurino]
Sorry, there were a bunch of things I had to do this week, so I’m a little tired.
[Megumi]
Kaho-chan, Sayaka-chan…
Oh, yes…?
[Kaho]
W-What is it?
[Sayaka]
Your performance at the Nadeshiko Festival was really good.
[Megumi]
Alright, bye.
M-Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
What about... our…
I’ve always wanted to be like Megu-chan.
[Rurino]
Whenever we tried out new things, she would always run ahead of me.
It’s really strange.
[Rurino]
Even back then, whenever I was alone with Megu-chan, I’d never run out of battery.
I decided to study abroad in California because of her.
[Rurino]
It always seemed like she could run anywhere she wanted to, so I wanted to catch up to her.
So I was really happy when she asked me to become a school idol with her.
[Rurino]
I thought that I could have fun with Megu-chan again.
But I…
[Rurino]
I never even noticed how much she was hurting…
B-But!
[Kaho]
That’s no way to talk to someone!
You went out of your way to meet with her, and she just shoos you away!?
[Kaho]
What kind of long-awaited reunion is that!? So rude!
Yeah…
[Rurino]
But, it was also my fault for suddenly showing up, so…
But, but!
[Kaho]
…Um… sorry…
Maybe…
[Rurino]
maybe she doesn’t like school idols anymore…
…I’m not so sure about that.
[Sayaka]
Sayaka-chan?
[Rurino]
I took a look at Megumi-senpai’s channel.
[Sayaka]
I noticed she’d uploaded a new video very recently, actually.
With that said, it’s time to look back on the last semester of the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
[Megumi]
Did you know?
Otomune Kozue and Yugiri Tsuzuri finally performed on stage together again!
[Megumi]
It was such an amazing performance, right!?
That wasn’t that long ago…
[Kaho]
Megumi-senpai knows quite a lot about you and me, too.
[Sayaka]
…So she’s cheering us on?
[Kaho]
I believe that if she truly hated the School Idol Club…
[Sayaka]
She wouldn’t spare all this time and effort to make these videos.
Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
Y’know…
Tsuzuri-senpai mentioned that it was because of the shock of her accident, right?
[Rurino]
That she’s fully recovered from her injury.
Yes.
[Sayaka]
So that means…
[Rurino]
If we can motivate her, she might be able to dance again, right?
Then… I want to try.
[Rurino]
I won’t give up like that ever again!
I won’t say that I want to quit the club!
[Rurino]
I definitely want Megu-chan to be a school idol again!
But how…?
[Kaho]
I have a great idea, actually!
[Rurino]
I call it…
The Grand Megu-chan Flaring Fire Plan!
[Rurino]