This isn’t quite what I had in mind…
[Sayaka]
How.. is it… Rurino-chan…?
[Kaho]
You… feel nice…?
It does, but I think it would be even nicer if you were a little more forceful~.
[Rurino]
Wait, even more than this…!?
[Kaho]
Sayaka-chan…
Okay, fine…
[Sayaka]
Ooh… ooh…!
[Rurino]
Sayaka-chan, your massages go hard, huh~
Why do I have to do this…!?
[Sayaka]
Hehehe…
[Kaho]
So, Rurino-chan…
Whaddya think?
[Kaho]
Nightly Sayaka-chan massages come free with your School Idol Club membership, you know~
Wait, I’d have this every night…!?
[Rurino]
I’m not doing that!
[Sayaka]
Hehe, she might say that, but you know…
[Kaho]
I’m serious! I’m not doing that!
[Sayaka]
Phew…
[Rurino]
The bath is nice and big, too…
Japan really is the best~…
[Rurino]
Ah, a little lower…
Ahhh, right there~.
[Rurino]
…Rurino-san and… Sayaka-san…?
[Kozue]
What on earth is going on here?
Huh!? K-Kozue-senpai! What brings you here!?
[Sayaka]
I thought I would do some stargazing for a homework assignment.
[Kozue]
I was just on my way out…
And you?
[Kozue]
This was just a short massage!
[Sayaka]
Ah, but it’s not what you think! This wasn’t my idea!
I see…
[Kozue]
Please don’t dismiss me without understanding what’s going on!
[Sayaka]
Kaho-san told me to do this!
That’s right, Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho]
Hehe.
This is actually just step one of my big plan to get more school idols.
[Kaho]
Rurino-chan was being invited to a bunch of other clubs by the girls in our class,
and it really looked like she was having a hard time deciding.
[Kaho]
…I see. So that’s what’s going on.
[Kozue]
Excuse me, could I have a moment of your time, Kaho-san?
Sure, what is it?
[Kaho]
I understand that you want her to join the School Idol Club, but you shouldn’t spoil her.
[Kozue]
Huh? Why not?
[Kaho]
It would be as if you were stringing her along, wouldn’t it?
[Kozue]
Wouldn’t you agree that it would be meaningless for her to opt to join our club when given a skewed perspective of our activities?
…I-I know you’re right, but…
[Kaho]
But you were pretty chummy with me when I started, weren’t you?
N-No, I wouldn’t say so.
[Kozue]
From the very beginning, I was…
Right, I was a proper demon with you.
[Kozue]
You only started being like that when you made me start doing morning exercises with you!
[Kaho]
I see…
[Kozue]
In other words, at the moment, you think of me as a demon, then?
In that case, I suppose it would only be fitting if I were to assign you more practice.
[Kozue]
You’re so mean! That was entrapment, I tell you! Entrapment!
[Kaho]
Anyway, jokes aside…
[Kozue]
If you want Rurino-san to join the School Idol Club, there surely should be other methods to convince her.
You are a school idol, after all.
[Kozue]
That… might be right, but still…
[Kaho]
But when you were trying to convince me, you really spoiled me…
…Just forget about that already. I’ll see you tomorrow.
[Kozue]
Something I can do because I’m a school idol, huh…
[Kaho]
Alright.
Let’s do what only we can do to get a new club member!
[Kaho]
Something that we can do because we’re school idols…?
[Sayaka]
What do you think it is, Sayaka-chan?
[Kaho]
…You’re not suggesting more massages, right?
[Sayaka]
Ahaha, what are you talking about? No, of course not, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
Listen, we’re school idols, right?
Even if it’s just practice, if we put on a cool enough show for her, then maybe she’ll start thinking that she wants to be like us!
[Kaho]
And if that happens, then she’ll probably be really motivated to join the club!
Kaho-san… what an actual, honest idea…
[Sayaka]
Yeah.
[Kaho]
Yesterday, Kozue-senpai gave me a great idea.
So…
[Kaho]
Do your best, Kozue-senpai! Tsuzuri-senpai!
Wait, what!?
[Sayaka]
I mean, we joined the club because we admired them, after all!
[Kaho]
But this would be the perfect time to say that you’ll do your best…
[Sayaka]
I will! Of course I’ll do my best, but…!
[Kaho]
Yeah, this is the perfect time for all of us to do our best! All four of us!
I’m not sure whether I should compliment you on that…
[Kozue]
Kozu always does her best, you know.
[Tsuzuri]
Are you going to just keep complimenting me for the rest of our lives?
[Kozue]
Are you okay with that?
I trust your “I’m okay”s now.
[Tsuzuri]
Right, but I was asking you if you were!
[Kozue]
…Oh, well. It looks like Rurino-san’s coming.
Mornin’!
[Rurino]
Looking forward to practicing with you guys from now on!!
Yeah, same here.
[Tsuzuri]
Um, what should we do today?
We usually have me working with Kaho-san, and you with Sayaka-san, but…
[Kozue]
Hm.
Since Rurino-san is here today, why don’t we second-years work as a group with all of the first-years?
[Kozue]
Alright.
[Tsuzuri]
Understood.
[Sayaka]
Thank you for your continued support and guidance.
You might not have the stamina to keep up at first, but let’s do our best as fellow sprouts, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Sure, sure! Please go easy on me, ‘mkay~?
[Rurino]
I’m quite surprised.
[Sayaka]
You’re very athletic, aren’t you, Rurino-san?
Have you taken dance lessons before?
[Tsuzuri]
Nah, I don’t do anything more special than walking to school.
[Rurino]
And I’ve only done some dance practice on my own.
Oh, that’s very impressive, then.
[Kozue]
You have good core strength, and your stamina is nothing to scoff at, either.
Guh… huff…
[Kaho]
Keep going, me…
Your finer movements, like those of your fingertips, are also quite graceful.
[Kozue]
You may have the potential to become a very popular school idol right away, Rurino-san.
Maybe I’ll even become the best before you even know it!?
[Rurino]
Heh, kidding! Might’ve gotten a lil’ carried away there!
We’ve got ourselves an up-and-comer here.
[Tsuzuri]
Agreed. I’m very excited to see it.
[Kozue]
I-I’ll do my best, too!
[Sayaka]
Oof…
[Kaho]
Me… three…
You have to develop more stamina, though, Kaho-san.
[Kozue]
You may end up falling behind not only Sayaka-san, but Rurino-san too.
No… way…!
[Kaho]
Saya, you’ve been really stiff lately.
[Tsuzuri]
Try to remember when you were as limber as freshly cooked rice.
Uh, I’ll try to do that…
[Sayaka]
Now then, shall we start practicing our singing?
[Kozue]
Aaaah!
[Rurino]
H-Huh!?
[Kozue]
I’m sorry! So sorry!
[Rurino]
I gotta go to the bathroom! Can I!?
Y-Yes, of course you can.
[Kozue]
We can continue the practice session when you come back.
Roger! So, um…
[Rurino]
If you’ll excuse me!
…Hasn’t she been gone for a pretty long time?
[Kaho]
You’re right.
[Kozue]
I wonder what’s going on.
Maybe…
[Tsuzuri]
She couldn’t find a bathroom, so she’s wandering around…?
I doubt it.
[Sayaka]
It’s just by the stairs, after all.
I-I’ll go check up on her!
[Kaho]
I’ll go, too!
[Sayaka]
It would be terrible if something were to have happened.
[Kozue]
Let’s join them in looking for her.
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
I looked in the bathroom near the stairs, but she wasn’t there!
[Kaho]
Did you find her, Sayaka-chan!?
About that…
[Sayaka]
I found this letter… in the club room…
Huh!?
[Kaho]
“Ruri is just a water flea.”
[Rurino]
What’s this!? What’s it supposed to mean!?
[Kaho]
She wasn’t human this whole time!?
No, I’m pretty sure she’s human…
[Sayaka]
Oh…
[Rurino]
Thankya…
Huh? Oh, sure.
[Kaho]
You’re welcome…
[Sayaka]
Wait, huh!?
Was that…!?
[Kaho]
Rurino-san!?
[Sayaka]