Hiya, everyone! I’m Osawa Rurino!
[Rurino]
Oh, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Looks like we’re in the same class!
So wait, that means that she visited our club room before she’d officially transferred in…
[Sayaka]
She must’ve been really motivated!
[Kaho]
You know what to do, right, Sayaka-chan?
Huh? What? Why do you look so serious?
[Sayaka]
Rurino-chan belongs to the School Idol Club, okay?
[Kaho]
So… what?
[Sayaka]
That means… that no matter what, we can’t let her get stolen away by any other club…
[Kaho]
She’s a very, very important new member of ours…!
Hmhm, it’ll be okay.
[Sayaka]
She was so enthusiastic about joining the club, after all.
I’m sure she’s already made up her mind.
[Sayaka]
Volleyball?
[Rurino]
Ooh, actually, that might be pretty fun, too!
Basketball?
[Rurino]
Not bad, not bad at all!
I’m pretty good at ball games, you know~?
[Rurino]
Kaho-san!? Why is she getting tempted so easily!?
[Sayaka]
Listen, Sayaka-chan…
[Kaho]
Not everyone in the world fully commits to things like you…
In fact, there’s a ton of people that can’t say no to an invitation!
[Kaho]
Like me!
Oh, no…
[Sayaka]
What should we do…?
Desperate times call for desperate measures…!
[Kaho]
Hey, hey, Osawa-san!
[Ena]
Wanna try out for the school choir~?
Choir? It’d feel good to sing really loudly, huh~!
[Rurino]
Hold it!
[Kaho]
Ah–! W-where’d you come from!?
[Ena]
Why are you butting in, Kaho-chan!?
H-Hey! You arrived pretty recently, right, Rurino-chan!?
[Kaho]
Sayaka-chan and I were planning on showing you around the place!
Oh, that’d be really nice!
[Rurino]
Let’s go, Rurino-chan! C’mon, hurry!
[Kaho]
Ah–! Hey!! We were just about to recruit a new club member–!
[Ena]
Seems like everyone had the same idea, huh…
[Sayaka]
Phew… thanks for that~.
[Rurino]
Hasunosora’s such a big school, I actually had trouble finding the club room yesterday…
Nah, it’s no problem!
[Kaho]
If I didn’t find it, I was just gonna give up and find another club to join.
[Rurino]
Ahaha, that was a close one~.
Since we’re on lunch break, I’m gonna show you every nook and cranny of this school!
[Kaho]
You’ll know everything like the back of your hand!
Woo~!
[Rurino]
Let’s start here!
[Kaho]
This is the School Idol Club’s room!
Okay! Gotcha!
[Rurino]
This is the school otter!
[Kaho]
Everyone likes feeding it, so it’s nice and chubby.
So kyute! Can I pet it!?
[Rurino]
And this is the warehouse…
[Kaho]
The club stores lots of older things in it, but…
It’s really easy to get lost, so make sure you’re always with someone in here, okay!?
[Kaho]
Huh~ What is this place?
[Rurino]
It’s like a haunted house~! Seems exciting!
Ah, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
You shouldn’t go any deeper in here!
We need to be back before lunch ends, you know!?
[Kaho]
A-And this is… gasp!
We ran into the School Idol Club room again!
[Kaho]
It’s the coolest, most fun, and the most amazing place in all of Hasunosora!
Kaho-san, you’re being extremely obvious!
[Sayaka]
Ahaha!
[Rurino]
Anyway, even though we’ve been to a bunch of places, there’s a lot of really important history to this school.
[Kaho]
History, huh…
[Rurino]
Honestly, I don’t really get that stuff.
I’d rather have sugary than history, anyway…
[Rurino]
Cogito, ergo Ruri.
Uh…
[Kaho]
I-I’m kinda the same way too, I think!
I’ve noticed how good the convenience store sweets are since I came back to the country…
[Rurino]
You’re so right!
[Kaho]
But those things have so many calories!
What are you talking about!?
[Rurino]
You know how bad the calories would get in America!?
My morning run went from being a hobby to a necessity!
[Rurino]
Huh!?
[Kaho]
…It feels like they have a lot in common.
[Sayaka]
Like, they both get so animated sometimes…
Did you say something, Sayaka-chan?
[Kaho]
Oh, nothing important.
[Sayaka]
I was just thinking how it’s like you’ve known each other for a long time.
Ehehe, Rurino-chan’s just really easy to talk to!
[Kaho]
Yeah, same here!
[Rurino]
Looks like it worked then!
I knew it’d be worth it to work hard to show up in Kaho-chan’s dreams every night~!
[Rurino]
Wait, are you haunting me!?
[Kaho]
You two really have gotten quite close, hehe.
[Sayaka]
Yes, yes! I’m fine, thank you! Best friend! Yaaay!
[Rurino]
W-Whoa! Did you hear that, Sayaka-chan!?
[Kaho]
That was actual English! She must’ve learned so much overseas!
I’m pretty sure I could understand more than I should have…
[Sayaka]
Wow!
[Kaho]
Keep saying stuff, Rurino-chan! Anything!
Hehe~!
[Rurino]
Okay, okay!
This is a pen!
[Rurino]
I’m school idol!
Very, very nice girl!
[Rurino]
Woo! Yeah!
[Kaho]
…Guh–…
[Rurino]
Rurino-san?
[Sayaka]
Wait… a… little…
[Rurino]
I’m… uh…
Ah, I think my battery is already out…
[Rurino]
Huh? What do you mean?
[Kaho]
Battery?
[Sayaka]
Sorry! I’ve got something I gotta do over in the second-year classrooms!
[Rurino]
You guys just go back, ‘kay? Goodbye!
…There she goes.
[Sayaka]
I wonder what got into her…
[Kaho]
Ah!
…No way!!
[Kaho]
Huh?
[Sayaka]
Is she trying to sneak around and check out the other clubs while we’re not looking!?
[Kaho]
We’ve gotta follow her!
But, Kaho-san…
[Sayaka]
Even if that were the case, she is free to choose what clubs she wishes to join…
But, Sayaka-chan…
[Kaho]
We finally found a new club member…
Even if you give me those puppy dog eyes, we shouldn’t do things we shouldn’t.
[Sayaka]
You’re not Tsuzuri-senpai…
I mean, of course I want her to join the School Idol Club, but even so…
[Sayaka]
…Okay, I understand, Sayaka-chan.
[Kaho]
So we shouldn’t interfere, but we do have to show just how much more charming the School Idol Club is than all the other clubs!
Huh?
[Sayaka]
Well, I guess…
Sure, that sounds about right!
[Sayaka]