Let’s go to the club room together, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
O-Okay.
[Rurino]
Let’s go, then, Kaho-chan.
Huh? Where’s Sayaka-chan?
[Rurino]
She went on ahead.
[Kaho]
Come on, Rurino-chan! Hurry, hurry!
You’re just as energetic as ever, huh, Kaho-chan…?
[Rurino]
…Oh no.
[Kaho]
Are you just about clocked out for today too…?
You’d think I was a new panda exhibit at the zoo with how much people wanted to talk to the new transfer…
[Rurino]
I-I see…
[Kaho]
But it’ll be okay!
We’ve got a special surprise for you!
[Kaho]
Surprise…?
[Rurino]
Now, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Feast your eyes on the reborn School Idol Club!
I mean you say that, but it looks completely the same to me…?
[Rurino]
Um, good afternoon…
What.
[Rurino]
Um, good afternoon…?
Oh, good–
[Tsuzuri]
Shhh, Tsuzuri-senpai! Not now!
[Sayaka]
Am I getting hazed?
[Rurino]
Heh heh heh…
[Kaho]
What do you think, Rurino-chan?
Everyone in the club’s gonna ignore you as much as possible.
[Kaho]
That way, even if you’re in the club room, it’ll be like you’re totally alone!
Total…
[Rurino]
Total?
[Kaho]
Total success?
Totally wrong…
[Rurino]
Wrong…!?
[Kaho]
O-Oh…
I knew this was a bad idea…
[Sayaka]
It’s fine, it’s fine!
[Kaho]
Okay, so for Plan B…
H-Hold on!
[Rurino]
What was this even supposed to be…?
Hey, since today’s our last chance, I figured I’d throw things at the wall and see what sticks.
[Kaho]
We wanted the School Idol Club to be a safe space for you!
We thought of plenty of ideas, so I hope you’re ready!
[Kaho]
H-Huh…?
[Rurino]
Why are you going this far…?
Well, even if we can’t come up with something good on our own,
[Kaho]
if we put our heads together, maybe we’ll figure something out!
It was like that with us too, after all.
[Tsuzuri]
…Right.
[Kozue]
That’s how it happened.
We were thinking of ways for you to keep going,
[Kaho]
so stuff like how to keep your battery charged or how to continue even if your battery does die!
Hey, could you please tell us more about yourself, Rurino-chan?
[Kaho]
I…
[Rurino]
Well, when I was in grade school…
I liked it when things were really fun.
[Rurino]
When everyone around me was smiling, the fun times would just keep going.
But that’s actually really difficult.
[Rurino]
Someone would get frustrated, and people would get upset.
And I would try to get everyone to get along…
[Rurino]
At first, it was just so I could make sure we could keep having fun,
but then I got completely used to doing it.
[Rurino]
It would always weigh on me.
I’d wonder if people in the group were getting bored or tired.
[Rurino]
And I would always tell myself that if someone was starting to feel that way,
I’d do whatever I had to to make sure they would have fun again.
[Rurino]
If you kept thinking like that, then you would…
[Sayaka]
Yeah…
[Rurino]
I’d wear myself out, right?
So I would spend more and more time by myself…
[Rurino]
I understand…
[Sayaka]
Interpersonal relations are very difficult, aren’t they…?
And then, one day, I realized something.
[Rurino]
Wow! Being alone is actually really fun!
Huh?
[Sayaka]
That’s not where I thought this was going…
I don’t have to worry about other people, and I can do whatever I want!
[Rurino]
The world’s my oyster! There’s nothing but fun to be had!
It’s a wonderful world!
[Rurino]
After that, I stopped holding myself back.
I like having fun, so…
[Rurino]
I would only chase after fun times! And then…!
Then, you joined the School Idol Club, right!?
[Kaho]
Uh, actually…
[Rurino]
Thanks for letting us know more about you, Rurino-chan.
[Kaho]
I didn’t know a thing about you until yesterday,
so I’m really happy you’ve told us so much.
[Kaho]
W-Well…
[Rurino]
But, you’ve found out now, when it’s already too late…
I…
[Rurino]
Yesterday, I said a lot of mean things that I shouldn’t have…
I don’t think of it like that.
[Kaho]
You thought it might be fun, so you decided to try being a school idol, right?
Then, we should think of a way for you to continue being one!
[Kaho]
…B-But…
[Rurino]
You know, I was this close to quitting school!
[Kaho]
Huh!? Why!?
[Rurino]
I thought that there was no way I could make my dreams come true here.
[Kaho]
But it was alright!
It turned out okay!
[Kaho]
Um…
[Rurino]
And I was very close to quitting this club myself.
[Sayaka]
Now, I’m working hard at both figure skating and being a school idol.
And until just recently, the second-years were fighting for like half a year!
[Kaho]
It wasn’t a fight.
[Kozue]
Your performance was so cool, Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
Is that your new life motto?
[Kozue]
…Why?
[Rurino]
Huh?
[Kaho]
From what you’ve been telling me, everyone here has such strong personalities.
[Rurino]
And yet, you all can go forward and be school idols together!? How!?
I’ve had to try so hard this long…
[Rurino]
How can you do it!?
Because…
[Kozue]
We’re school idols!
[Kaho]
Because you’re school idols…?
[Rurino]
Yeah!
[Kaho]
School idols are amazing.
No matter what they do, they do so freely!
[Kaho]
You can do it for yourself, or for the people that support you,
or to win Love Live!, or even just for fun!
[Kaho]
Everyone’s different, so sometimes our ideas might clash, and maybe we’ll get into arguments…
But we’re all school idols, so we can acknowledge each other and move forward, hand in hand.
[Kaho]
As long as you want to, it doesn’t matter what kind of personality you have.
You’ll still be a school idol!
[Kaho]
So, Rurino-chan?
Don’t you want to try being a school idol?
[Kaho]
If you want to, of course, we’ll give you our full support!
Because we’re all in this together, as girls who love school idols!
[Kaho]
I…
[Rurino]
I want to try.
Even if you’re not the same, you can still face forward and have fun together.
[Rurino]
I came here because the Hasunosora School Idol Club is what I aspire to be, so…
I want to try being a school idol!
[Rurino]
I’ve been watching all this time, even when I was in California!
And I always thought that it looked so fun!
[Rurino]
And as I watched the club, I realized that I wanted to be a part of it!
To be the same, yet completely different…
[Rurino]
I’m the same, so I thought that as long as I’m together with all of you, maybe I might be able to do it.
Can I…
[Rurino]
Can I be a school idol too…?
Of course you can.
[Sayaka]
Even someone like me could come this far, after all.
I’m sure you can.
[Tsuzuri]
We’re all here for you.
As long as you want to, you’ll be able to be a school idol.
[Kozue]
But I can’t be around people without my battery running dry,
[Rurino]
and I’m the disrespectful water flea that ditched practice…
And most of all, I love being alone.
[Rurino]
But you have fun when you’re together with everyone too, right?
[Kaho]
I know that about you now, Rurino-chan!
…Am I not going to be a bother…?
[Rurino]
Of course not!
[Kaho]
Running out of battery is just part of you, Rurino-chan!
Even if a flower bed has loads of different flowers, it doesn’t make it any less beautiful!
[Kaho]
I want to be a school idol with you, Rurino-chan!
…Yeah! I do too!
[Rurino]
Thanks, Kaho-chan.
And everyone…
[Rurino]
I’m fine, thank you!
Hehehe…
[Kaho]
Oh, right!
We never talked about that surprise we had!
[Kaho]
Huh?
[Rurino]
There’s still something else?
Hehehe…
[Kaho]
Ta-da!
I call it the loner house!
[Kaho]
…What.
[Rurino]
So what do you think!? As long as you’re in there, you can be alone, no matter when!
[Kaho]
And the inside’s dark and cramped, so I’m sure it’ll be relaxing! Nice idea, isn’t it!?
Total…
[Rurino]
Total? Totally awesome!?
[Kaho]
Totally wrong!!!
[Rurino]
Wha–!?
[Kaho]
In any case, I’d like to become a full-fledged member, so…
[Rurino]
W-What do you say to that!?
Naturally, we accept.
[Kozue]
It’s fine if your battery dies.
If anything, being able to communicate is more than enough.
[Kozue]
Right, Tsuzuri?
I can do that now, right?
[Tsuzuri]
That’s because Sayaka-san has worked very, very hard.
[Kozue]
I’ve gotten pretty used to it recently, so you’re fine.
[Sayaka]
Ahahaha, that’s pretty funny!
[Rurino]
She laughed. Nice job.
[Tsuzuri]
By the way, what do you want to do, Rurino-chan?
[Kaho]
Our club does activities in subunits, right?
Are you asking whether she should learn under Kozue-senpai or Tsuzuri-senpai?
[Sayaka]
Huh? Oh, nah!
[Rurino]
I’ll go with Megu-chan!
I came back to Japan for her, after all!
[Rurino]
…Megu-chan?
[Kaho]
Wait, who are you referring to?
[Sayaka]
Huh!?
[Rurino]