I’m sorry for giving you guys the runaround.
[Rurino]
I really meant it when I said it was fun, though! Seriously!
Rurino-chan, wait! This is all too sudden!
[Kaho]
But… look, you know what they say about nipping buds.
[Rurino]
I figured I’d do it now before I… you know, make things worse…
B-But!
[Sayaka]
If that’s the case, then why join the School Idol Club in the first place!?
Didn’t you have something you wanted to do!?
[Sayaka]
That’s…
[Rurino]
I wanted to… with Megu-chan…
Huh?
[Sayaka]
…No, it’s nothing.
[Rurino]
Sorry.
I should’ve known this wouldn’t…
[Rurino]
Hey, Rurino-chan.
[Kaho]
I understand you enjoy being alone.
When I was really young, I was really frail,
[Kaho]
so I would spend every day reading in my room.
And I still like reading, even now.
[Kaho]
But…
I didn’t want to just keep living like that, because I wanted to blossom!
[Kaho]
I…
[Rurino]
I think I’d rather not cause trouble for others…
You all had to interrupt practice because of me.
[Rurino]
I’m really sorry.
Ah, but well, we’re still in the same class, so…
[Rurino]
If we could… um… stay friends…
I think I’d really appreciate that.
[Rurino]
…Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Wait, please!
Please, just give it another chance!
[Kaho]
Another chance…?
[Rurino]
One more time!
[Kaho]
Come to the club room, just one more time!
Please!
[Kaho]
Wouldn’t you hate it if things ended this way!?
I…
[Rurino]
Consider it a request from me as well, Rurino-san.
[Sayaka]
It might just be me, but…
I think there’s a difference between enjoying being alone and becoming isolated.
[Sayaka]
So…
Please!
[Kaho]
I’m sorry you have to keep worrying about me.
[Rurino]
N-No, that’s not what…
[Kaho]
But…
[Rurino]
Alright, I understand.
Just…
[Rurino]
Don’t force yourself to do anything for me, okay?
You don’t have to worry about me being alone.
[Rurino]
Come now, Kaho-san.
[Kozue]
Huh?
[Kaho]
Oh, Kozue-senpai.
I was very surprised to hear you suddenly left school on a bus.
[Kozue]
I managed to smooth things over with the dorm mother, but…
What on earth happened?
[Kozue]
Kozue-senpai…
[Kaho]
Kozue-senpai…!
Huh? Wait, what’s… going on?
[Kozue]
Here.
Oh, thank you…
[Kaho]
It’s nice and warm.
It’s hard to fathom that Rurino-san harbored such a side of her…
[Kozue]
From looking at her, I fully believed she was a cheerful, positive girl…
You truly can’t judge a book by its cover.
[Kozue]
But to think she’d had that application of resignation on her this whole time.
I suppose that means that somewhere inside her,
[Kozue]
she’s always felt that doing this would be impossible for her…
Kaho-san, could you come over here?
[Kozue]
Huh?
[Kaho]
The sky is clear tonight, so the stars are quite visible.
[Kozue]
Please, take a look through this telescope.
Um…
[Kaho]
Okay.
Whoa… Amazing…
[Kaho]
I didn’t think there were this many stars I couldn’t normally see…!
Hmhm, fascinating, isn’t it?
[Kozue]
We will soon be on summer vacation, won’t we?
Since I’d received a self-research assignment,
[Kozue]
I thought I’d start on it right away.
Oof…
[Kaho]
Summer… homework…
That’s why I had this telescope taken out and sent here from home.
[Kozue]
Oh, so this isn’t school property? It’s yours?
[Kaho]
Correct.
[Kozue]
I can’t explain why, but I’ve always liked stargazing.
There are very few stars visible to the naked eye.
[Kozue]
Regardless, the sky is always full of stars.
I believe that school idols are similar.
[Kozue]
My goal is, naturally, to shine as brightly as the brightest first-magnitude star, though.
Kaho-san…
[Kozue]
I wonder what star you want to be like?
I…
[Kaho]
Um, Kozue-senpai…
Could I ask you something…?
[Kaho]
Of course.
[Kozue]
This… isn’t enough to properly thank you for before, but…
I’ve felt you’ve had something to say for a while.
[Kozue]
I don’t understand how Rurino feels at all.
[Kaho]
But I realized something when I had time to think about it by myself.
I figured… I probably didn’t even try to understand.
[Kaho]
I was only focused on how much I wanted new members for the club.
So much so that I only saw Rurino-chan as just a possible new member.
[Kaho]
But each school idol is different…
Just like the stars.
[Kaho]
There’s no one out there that exists just to be a new member!
You’re right.
[Kozue]
Next time, I’ll definitely talk to Rurino-chan properly!
[Kaho]
And… thank you, Kozue-senpai, for always looking after me and always spoiling me!
W-What’s with the sudden thanks…?
[Kozue]
And for the last time, I do not spoil you.
So, um…
[Kaho]
If you can, there’s something I could use your help with, Kozue-senpai!
Of course I can, but…
[Kozue]
This isn’t me spoiling you, okay?
I simply have a responsibility as club president to hear out any request from my club members.
[Kozue]
Ehehe, thanks, Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho]
And!
I might not know what kind of star I want to be like yet, but!
[Kaho]
I want to make up a big constellation in the sky together with everyone!
And to do that, we need Rurino-chan to be with us!
[Kaho]