I finally made it here…
[Rurino]
Hasunosora!
After a year and a half, I’m back in Japan!
[Rurino]
Y’know, I didn’t expect this…
I see…
[Rurino]
It’s kinda hot, huh!
Wait, it’s even hotter here than in California!
[Rurino]
It’s so… humid and muggy…
Yep, this is a Japanese summer, alright…
[Rurino]
Hm? What?
You need somethin’?
[Rurino]
‘Kay, ‘kay, what is it, most welcome foreign guest?
You wanna know how to get from here to Kanazawa?
[Rurino]
Uh, well!
Wait!
[Rurino]
Little wait, please!
Uh…! Um…!
[Rurino]
This! This way!
Go straight! Over!
[Rurino]
Yes, yes!
Okay, okay!
[Rurino]
Go!
Thank you, thank you!
[Rurino]
Oh, yes!
You’re welcome!
[Rurino]
Oh?
Are you inviting me to take a taxi together if I’m also going to Kanazawa Station…?
[Rurino]
Mm…!
Thank you, thank you!
[Rurino]
Bye-bye! Goodbye!
Good luck! Have a nice day!
[Rurino]
Haa…
Maybe I should’ve said yes…
[Rurino]
But I don’t think I can last inside a car like that…
Never know when I’ll run out of battery…
[Rurino]
Welp…
Guess I’m taking the bus alone…
[Rurino]
But I’m looking forward to this…
Hasunosora School Idol Club.
[Rurino]
…I hope I’ll have a fun time there.
It was really cool seeing you and
Tsuzuri-senpai on stage together~…
[Kaho]
Well, thank you…
[Kozue]
But Kaho-san, while I am glad to hear you say that…
That was a while ago now, you know?
[Sayaka]
I remember it like it was yesterday~…
[Kaho]
Good memory.
[Tsuzuri]
You’re very smart.
I don’t think that’s what she meant…
[Kozue]
We’ve gained quite a number of
subscribers on our channel recently.
[Sayaka]
Good job, Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho & Sayaka]
Why are you two encouraging me so forcefully?
[Kozue]
Nice, Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
Not you too! Knock it off!
[Kozue]
It looks like you’re fully back to your usual self, Kozue-senpai.
[Sayaka]
…I think so too, Sayaka-san.
[Kozue]
I’ve caused a great deal of trouble for you all,
but I am truly grateful.
[Kozue]
No, it’s okay. Don’t worry about it, K-Kozue-senpai.
[Sayaka]
I’m glad you two are getting closer!
[Kaho]
And that’s why…
I think it’d be a great time to invite new members to the club!
[Kaho]
New members?
[Sayaka]
Yeah.
[Kaho]
“Dream Believers” is really a song for three subunits to sing, right?
Oh, that’s what you mean.
[Sayaka]
Right!?
[Kaho]
And because of that, if we get some new members, we’ll be able to have a perfect performance of “Dream Believers”!
I wonder what that’d look like!
[Kaho]
I’m sure it would be an even more amazing performance!
[Sayaka]
Another subunit, huh…
[Tsuzuri]
…Well, no matter the case, we might get new members with the new batch of students next year.
[Kozue]
Huh!? I can’t wait that long!
[Kaho]
Where can we find new members…?
Oh, Tsuzuri-senpai, you wouldn’t happen to have two twin sisters, would you?
[Kaho]
Don’t say something so terrifying…
[Sayaka]
What a nightmare.
[Kozue]
What am I to you?
[Tsuzuri]
Excuse meeee!
[Rurino]
Is this the School Idol Club!?
Y-Yes, it is…
[Kozue]
But, who are you…?
Osawa Rurino! And I’m looking to join!
[Rurino]
We…
[Kaho]
We got a new applicant~!
I’m Osawa Rurino, and this month, I transferred to Hasunosora!
[Rurino]
That makes me the firstest of first-years!
Huh… So you’ve been going to school in California until just recently.
[Kozue]
Yes!
[Rurino]
I actually planned to come in during summer break, but I couldn’t wait any longer so I dipped!
Ah, I mean I decided to return immediately!
[Rurino]
It’s alright, you don’t need to be so stiff.
[Kozue]
Just speak as you normally would.
Yeah, yeah!
[Kaho]
It’s nice to meet you, Rurino-chan!
Alright, I’ll take you up on that, then!
[Rurino]
What’s up? You can call me Ruri for short!
Hiya, Ruri.
[Tsuzuri]
You certainly are adaptable…
[Sayaka]
Um…
It’s a pleasure to meet you, Rurino-san.
[Sayaka]
So anyway, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
Why’d you decide to come here?
And also, what made you decide to become a school idol!?
[Kaho]
I’m interested in that as well.
[Kozue]
Could it have been… our recent performance?
[Sayaka]
‘Cuz it seemed fun!
[Rurino]
I-It seemed fun…?
[Sayaka]
I totally get you!
[Kaho]
School idols are amazing, right!?
Yeah, yeah!
[Rurino]
You were all fired up like, “wow!” and then you felt so cool, like, “whoa!” and you were all so sparkly and shiny!
I thought you all shone so bright! It was so impressive how amazing you were!
[Rurino]
Cogito! Ergo Ruri!
Right, right!? That’s exactly it!
[Kaho]
And I love having fun,
[Rurino]
so I thought that I really wanted to be a school idol and I rushed back here!
I see…
[Kozue]
But you came to think that way from watching a broadcast of our performance, right?
I’m glad to hear it.
[Kozue]
Nice, Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
Again, that’s enough of that.
[Kozue]
Thank you for your application, Rurino-san.
I accept.
[Kozue]
Hm… though, seeing as you’ve just transferred in,
I suppose starting you off with our full regimen might be too much, huh?
[Kozue]
You’re still getting accustomed to your new classes, too.
You… have a point!
[Rurino]
Therefore, I believe we should start you off on a trial period.
[Kozue]
That way, you can freely attend whenever you have the time.
You can steadily grow accustomed to being a member of our club.
[Kozue]
Thanks for lookin’ out for me!
[Rurino]
I’ve got no problem with that, so I’m all welcome to it!
Actually, I’m thankful you didn’t have me go through some sort of entrance exam!
[Rurino]
If there was something like that, I wouldn’t be here, ahaha~
[Kaho]
You shouldn’t be proud of that!
[Sayaka]
Ahaha!
[Rurino]
‘Kay then! Lookin’ forward to joining you guys as a trial member!
Yeah!
[Kaho]