H-Hey! Rurino-chan!!
[Kaho]
What was that farewell letter supposed to mean!?
Huh…?
[Rurino]
Guh–!?
She… she’s running away!?
[Sayaka]
Why!?
[Kaho]
Can you not follow me!?
[Rurino]
Hey, why’d you ditch practice!?
[Kaho]
Do you hate singing that much!?
Or maybe she’s not feeling well!?
[Sayaka]
But isn’t she running too fast for that!?
[Kaho]
There’s no way she’s sick! No way!
Then why is she running away!?
[Sayaka]
And why are we chasing her!?
If she’s running away, isn’t it only natural to chase after her!?
[Kaho]
I don’t get it!
[Sayaka]
Agh, give it up already!
[Rurino]
Wait, is she getting on that bus!?
[Sayaka]
Kaho-san, if we keep going, then–
Let’s go, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
But why!?
[Sayaka]
Agh… haaah…
[Rurino]
I-I can’t believe… you chased me all the way here…
…Why?
[Rurino]
I don’t get it at all, either…
[Sayaka]
B-Because… you just went… and ran away from us…
[Kaho]
What’s… wrong?
Is… something wrong…?
[Kaho]
I’m just guessing, but…
[Sayaka]
I’d bet that Kaho-san would have chased you to the ends of the earth until you sat down and talked to her…
She’s very passionate…
[Sayaka]
I’m so sorry!
[Rurino]
Huh!?
[Sayaka & Kaho]
Ahh…
[Rurino]
Now this is summer…
Wh-wh-whoa!
[Kaho]
All the soda’s spilling out!
Hey, is this really the time for ramune!?
[Sayaka]
Umm, I am… terribly sorry for causing this incident…
[Rurino]
I truly had intended on immediately returning to practice. However…
I instead have caused considerable inconvenience for all parties, including Mistress Kozue and Mistress Tsuzuri.
[Rurino]
Therefore, I must offer my humblest apologies…
I’ve never heard such a corporate apology before…
[Kaho]
I am just a water flea, so…
[Rurino]
…Wait, why are we at the batting cages?
[Sayaka]
U-Uh, well!
[Kaho]
It’s my first time coming to one of these places! It’s actually kinda fun, huh!
Hahaha, it sure is!
[Rurino]
…Haaah.
I can’t do this…
[Rurino]
My battery’s fully drained.
Um…
[Sayaka]
What started all this…?
Huh? Is it so bad you can’t talk about it!?
[Kaho]
Ah, no, it’s not…
[Rurino]
I’m just… not in social mode right now.
What!?
[Kaho]
By any chance, Rurino-san…
[Sayaka]
Have you been forcing yourself this whole time?
Huh?
[Kaho]
Not really, but…
[Rurino]
Well… ah…
Yeah, sure… that.
[Rurino]
She clearly gave up on explaining!
[Kaho]
Rurino-san.
[Sayaka]
I don’t mind talking about it, but…
[Rurino]
It’s just nothin’ special, y’know?
Would you… talk to us about it?
[Sayaka]
I’ll keep a tab on Kaho-san.
Huh!?
[Kaho]
…I really like it when things are lively,
[Rurino]
but when they’re always like that, I tend to get drained really easily…
And that’s not because…
[Sayaka]
you were forcing yourself… to be with us…?
Nah.
[Rurino]
I’m totally serious when I say the School Idol Club is really fun,
and you’re all such nice people.
[Rurino]
It’s just…
When people start caring about me, I try to give them as much care in return,
[Rurino]
and that starts draining my battery even faster.
And now I’m just in airplane mode.
[Rurino]
So you worry too much about other people?
[Kaho]
If it’s like that, you don’t have to worry about us!
Nah…
[Rurino]
It’s hard for me not to…
I…
[Sayaka]
I think I somewhat understand where you’re coming from.
But… that’s why…!
[Kaho]
You don’t have to work yourself this hard…!
Look, I really get that.
[Rurino]
I just… can’t.
No matter what I’ve tried, nothing changes.
[Rurino]
And since we all take the time to get together, it’s not just about me.
I want everyone to have fun, too.
[Rurino]
I see…
[Kaho]
Ahaha…
[Rurino]
It doesn’t help anyone if I’m like this, y’know.
So this is your…
[Sayaka]
“dead battery mode,” is it, Rurino-san?
This seems very serious…
[Sayaka]
When I’m like this, I can’t really do much…
[Rurino]
Just gotta sit tight and wait to recharge…
And I would hate to make other people worry about me.
[Rurino]
‘Cause then you’d all have to cover for me, and then you’d start having less fun…
So, I figured it’d be best for me to stick to myself…
[Rurino]
Rurino-san…
[Sayaka]
Ah, but listen!
[Rurino]
I don’t want you to get it twisted!
I’m totally fine being alone.
[Rurino]
Things like having a solo batting cage outing can feel like a royal feast to me.
Yakiniku also became much easier solo, so in fact, I welcome it.
[Rurino]
So, I’m totally, completely, one hundred percent fine with being alone!
I’m not pretending or anything.
[Rurino]
I can find my own fun, all by myself.
Seriously!
[Rurino]
Sorry ‘bout making this whole thing all weird, okay!
Everything’s so awkward now ‘cuz of me…
[Rurino]
Ahaha…
So, um.
[Rurino]
Take this.
W-Wait, Rurino-san.
[Sayaka]
Is that…
a club resignation application…!?
[Sayaka]
Huuuuh!?
[Kaho]