Clear, blue skies!
[Kaho]
Stretching out over the seas!
We’re at the beach!
[Kaho]
Sorry for the inconvenience, Kozue-senpai.
[Sayaka]
Thank you for providing us with accommodation for this trip.
It’s not a problem. This is a vacation home for our use.
[Kozue]
I didn’t know you were rich, Kozue-senpai.
[Rurino]
No wonder you got such a sparkly aura!
Hehe, this isn’t even the whole of how amazing Kozue-senpai is!
[Kaho]
There’s more!?
[Rurino]
I’d bet she has over 300 vacation homes just like this one!
[Kaho]
Whoa!!
[Rurino]
No, I don’t.
[Kozue]
But Saya’s amazing, too.
[Tsuzuri]
She can make really tasty stew.
Would you quit throwing me into these sorts of comparisons!?
[Sayaka]
Alright, everyone! Let’s take our bags inside!
Okay~!
[Kaho & Tsuzuri & Rurino]
Wow! Amazing!
[Rurino]
The bed’s so big.
[Tsuzuri]
A kitchen as spacious as this would be so easy to use…!
[Sayaka]
It’s like the Dragon Palace…!
[Kaho]
What an excellent vacation house!
[Rurino]
Kozue-senpai, I’m moving in here permanently, as of today.
[Kaho]
I’m sure I’ll be able to blossom here…!
The air might be too salty, though…
[Kozue]
My mother used to use this house for musical composition, actually.
Because of that, the house is very well soundproofed.
[Kozue]
We should be able to practice even well into the night.
Huh…? Practice… well into the night…?
[Kaho]
B-But the beach…
There’s no need to be worried.
[Kozue]
Of course we’ll be going there, too.
Yay! Love you, Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho]
How can you throw that out so casually…?
[Kozue]
Anyway, where are Tsuzuri and Sayaka-san?
Well…
[Rurino]
Tsuzuri-senpai looked really happy sleeping on that really big bed.
And Sayaka-chan was so moved by the kitchen that she’s just been standing there.
[Rurino]
Oh, and Kaho-san’s just run off after changing into her swimsuit.
Alright, beach time!
[Kaho]
Time to have fun~!
…I see.
[Kozue]
Everyone’s scattered off to do whatever they want, but they can still face the same goal and have fun…
[Rurino]
This must be what the Hasunosora School Idol Club is all about!
…Yes, that’s right!
[Kozue]
Okay, fine.
I guess no one’s in the mood for practice right now,
[Kozue]
so let’s start by having fun at the beach.
Let’s call Tsuzuri and Sayaka-san and head there together.
[Kozue]
‘Kaaay!
[Rurino]
Alright, that’s enough playing around.
[Kozue]
It’s about time we start practicing.
Okaaay!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Rurino]
What’s the plan for today?
[Sayaka]
Our goal is to have a successful performance, so I suppose the second-years should prioritize Rurino-san’s training?
About that…
[Kozue]
Ah! Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Oh.
[Megumi]
Kaho-chan, Sayaka-chan! To catch!
[Rurino]
On it!
[Kaho]
You’re not getting away!
[Sayaka]
W-Wah–!
[Megumi]
What’s up with you two!?
…Oh, come on.
[Megumi]
I’m your senior, you know?
What are you doing here, Megu-chan!?
[Rurino]
Huh? W-Well, y’see…
[Megumi]
since we’re on summer break, I figured I’d go check out the beach, so I…
happened to be looking around?
[Megumi]
Huh? It was a coincidence…!?
[Rurino]
There’s no way!
[Kaho]
She’s gotta be lying!
Oh, yeah, that makes sense…
[Rurino]
I just automatically believed it because it was Megu-chan…
Do you not feel any shame in lying to Rurino-san like that, Megumi-senpai?
[Sayaka]
Kozue! Aren’t your first-years being way too hard on me!?
[Megumi]
They can make their own decisions.
[Kozue]
Anyway, Tsuzuri and I invited Megumi here.
I thought she should look over Rurino-san’s practice.
[Kozue]
Huh!?
[Kaho & Sayaka & Megumi & Rurino]
H-Hold it, Kozue! You never told me that!
[Megumi]
Oh, did I not?
[Kozue]
Kozu can be pretty forgetful sometimes, you know.
[Tsuzuri]
Are you really gonna do it, Megumi-senpai!?
[Kaho]
I didn’t know you were that nice!
Ugh…
[Megumi]
But it seems we have no other choice, hm, Kaho-san?
[Kozue]
I’m part of Cerise Bouquet, and Tsuzuri’s part of DOLLCHESTRA.
We just don’t have enough second-years.
[Kozue]
Guess it has to be this way.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s just how it goes.
Grr… You deceitful little…
[Megumi]
So what do you say, Megumi?
[Kozue]
Megu-chan… won’t you teach me more about school idols…?
[Rurino]
…I’m very out of practice, you know?
[Megumi]
But you’ve been watching school idols all this time, haven’t you?
[Kozue]
Megu-chan…
[Rurino]
…Okay, fine!
[Megumi]
Just don’t blame me if it turns out badly!
Yaaay! Love you, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
Hmmm…
[Kaho]
…There’s no other choice.
[Sayaka]
At least Rurino-san seems quite happy.
…Fine!
[Kaho]
Kozue-senpai, let’s hurry up and get to practice already!
Oh, that’s rare.
[Kozue]
We should go too, Saya.
[Tsuzuri]
Okay!
[Sayaka]
Alright, Megu-chan! Let’s do this!
[Rurino]
I’m just gonna say this, okay!
[Megumi]
Huh…?
[Rurino]
W-What is it?
…I’m… sorry I was so rude the other day.
[Megumi]
And… congrats on getting into Hasunosora.
Yeah!
[Rurino]