I… I went too hard…
[Kaho]
I shouldn’t have… run that much along with those two…
I played at the beach all morning…
[Kaho]
and then we did so much practice…
my HP is pretty much zero now…
[Kaho]
The beach is terrifying…
The temptation to play too much is too strong…
[Kaho]
Rurino-san, I know it isn’t much, but I wanted to help in whatever way I could, so I tried looking it up.
[Sayaka]
Even if a physical injury is healed, the mental trauma left behind can prevent someone from returning to performing.
This occasionally happens to figure skaters as well.
[Sayaka]
I see…
[Rurino]
That can still be healed… right?
Yes, of course.
[Sayaka]
However, the way that happens varies from person to person, so…
One thing I will say, Rurino-san, is that your plan to bring back her drive to perform…
[Sayaka]
is something that has already been shown to be effective.
Oh, really!
[Rurino]
Thanks, Sayaka-chan!
But…
[Sayaka]
…But?
[Rurino]
Well, the thing is…
[Sayaka]
While it is true that a fun performance can help her overcome her trauma,
the reverse is also possible…
[Sayaka]
That is to say, if your performance were to end in failure…
It is very probable that it would only exacerbate the problem.
[Sayaka]
It’s also very likely Kozue-senpai falling from the stage a few months ago also made Megumi-senpai’s trauma resurface.
And although nothing serious came of the incident,
[Sayaka]
I’m sure that you mean a lot to Megumi-senpai…
so…
[Sayaka]
If I… were to fail…
[Rurino]
Don’t worry, Sayaka-chan!
There’s no way I could fail.
[Rurino]
I… see…
[Sayaka]
This is for Megu-chan, after all!
[Rurino]
I’m sure you can see just how pretty she is, and how good her fashion sense is,
and how nice her voice is, and how amazing her smile is, right?
[Rurino]
H-Huh? Um…
[Sayaka]
Not only that, but she has the smarts and incredible moves.
[Rurino]
And her conversations are always so interesting that she always draws a crowd with them!
And she even used to be a TV personality, too!
[Rurino]
She’s shown up on a bunch of TV shows!
O-Oh, I see…
[Sayaka]
Yeah!
[Rurino]
She can do anything, and she’s always been amazing!
That’s why everything will turn out okay!
[Rurino]
I’m sure that she’ll be able to overcome this, too!
[Sayaka]
I… I believe in her.
…You share a strong bond, hm?
[Sayaka]
Of course, we’ve been together since grade school!
[Rurino]
Alright!
The training camp isn’t over yet, so why don’t we get to bed!
[Rurino]
Or maybe you guys wanna do something else? Like a classic pillow fight?
Hehe… I’m pretty good at those, you know.
[Sayaka]
Oh, so you think you can handle it, huh!?
[Rurino]
I’m sure.
[Sayaka]
Back when I was following in my sister’s footsteps,
I used to go to figure skating training camps fairly often.
[Sayaka]
It was a regular occurrence with the other kids my age when we would stay in a big room together.
Alright, in that case!
[Rurino]
Kaho-chan, let’s go!
H-Huh…?
[Kaho]
B-But my body’s still so sore, and–
Here goes!
[Sayaka]
Yeet!
[Rurino]
Wha–!?
[Kaho]
…Kaho-san…?
[Sayaka]
…Yikes, did we kill her!?
[Rurino]
Fine!
[Kaho]
If that’s how you wanna do this, then I’ll use up all my energy for tomorrow, right here, right now!
I’m gonna make you blossom!
[Kaho]
Bring it on!
Aah!
[Sayaka]
Ahaha!
[Rurino]
Ahahaha!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Rurino]
…haa… haa…
[Megumi]
Yeah. And then we can have fun together again!
Yeah! Let’s have fun together again, Megu-chan!
[Rurino]
I’ll definitely catch up to you!
…Seriously, what am I doing?
[Megumi]
Why am I still like this…?