I’m going to put on an amazing performance during summer break!
[Rurino]
Huh!?
[Sayaka]
Megu-chan would never miss a performance from the Hasunosora School Idol Club!
[Rurino]
To motivate Megu-chan, I decided that I’d have to work hard on myself first!
So I figured that the best way to light a fire in her heart would be to do a special summer performance!
[Rurino]
Nice, Rurino-chan…!
[Kaho]
I think that’s a great idea!
Isn’t it!?
[Rurino]
A live performance, huh?
[Kozue]
I agree.
However…
[Kozue]
It will be considerably difficult doing a live performance so soon after joining the club, even for you.
Doubly so if you aim to move someone’s heart.
[Kozue]
That just means I’ll need our veterans to bring on lots of special training!
[Rurino]
Oh…?
[Kozue]
Special, you say...?
You can’t just say things like that to Kozue-senpai, Rurino-chan!
[Kaho]
She’ll squeeze you dry, you know!?
Your dried flower has certainly flourished, wouldn’t you say, Kaho-san?
[Kozue]
Eek…!
[Kaho]
Hey.
[Tsuzuri]
What is it, Tsuzuri-senpai?
[Sayaka]
Do you need a nap?
No?
[Tsuzuri]
What am I to you?
Well, anyway.
[Tsuzuri]
I want us to do a training camp.
Training camp…?
[Sayaka]
Last year, we talked about maybe going to the beach.
[Tsuzuri]
The beach!?
[Kaho]
Now that you mention it…
[Kozue]
The plan ended up falling through, though.
I’m surprised you remember.
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
Since then, every day I wondered when we would go to the beach.
I see…
[Kozue]
She’s almost like a little girl waiting for a letter from Santa…
[Sayaka]
Huh!? The beach!? I wanna go to the beach!
[Kaho]
You too, right, Rurino-chan!? Right!?
Yeah.
[Rurino]
Listening to the raging tides in total solitude on a winter’s beach is the best!
Wait, that’s not what I was thinking of at all!
[Kaho]
Gah-... Um…
[Rurino]
But, well… Even if the beach ends up being completely filled with people…
I still wanna do a training camp!
[Rurino]
Um… will you be okay with that?
[Sayaka]
It’s just…
I expect you might have to spend a lot more time with other people than normal,
[Sayaka]
so you might run out of battery…
It’ll probably happen!
[Rurino]
Huh!?
[Sayaka]
But I’m doing all of this for Megu-chan,
[Rurino]
so even if it might happen, I still wanna do it!
For the Megu-chan Flaring Fire Plan…!
[Rurino]
Oh… but maybe I might end up causing trouble for everyone…
I’ll do everything I can to make sure I don’t end up becoming a water flea, so…
[Rurino]
Kozue-senpai, Tsuzuri-senpai, I’m leaving it all up to you!
Please train me well!
[Rurino]
Very well, leave it to me.
[Kozue]
This summer, all of us will hold a training camp.
Yay!!! Beach time!!!
[Kaho]
T-This is very nice, right, Tsuzuri-senpai?
[Sayaka]
You’ve had to wait a year for this…
…Wait.
[Sayaka]
If we’re going to hold a training camp, does that mean…
I’ll have to look after her the whole time…?
[Sayaka]
Training camp!
[Rurino]
Beach!
[Kaho]
B-Babysitting…
[Sayaka]
What’s wrong with me…?
[Megumi]
I can do it in practice, but…
Megumi.
[Kozue]
…Ugh.
[Megumi]
Kozue, Tsuzuri, what is it?
Whatever our relationship might be right now, I don’t think it warrants an “ugh.”
[Kozue]
You watched our recent performance, didn’t you?
Aren’t you interested in how Rurino-san is doing?
[Kozue]
No? I don’t have anything to do with the School Idol Club anymore.
[Megumi]
What she does is none of my business.
Ruri’s gonna be performing solo next time.
[Tsuzuri]
Huh!? Isn’t it way too soon for that!?
[Megumi]
She wouldn’t have the stamina for it, so she ought to do more foundational training…!
Ah.
[Megumi]
B-But it’s not like I care about that or anything!
It’s what Rurino-san wanted.
[Kozue]
She said that she needed to show a certain someone her performance, no matter what.
Hm…?
[Megumi]
Hey, Megu.
[Tsuzuri]
Kozu and I performed together.
Seems so.
[Megumi]
We made a promise to each other when we decided to retire from Nationals, right?
[Tsuzuri]
That we would never be involved with each other ever again.
You even said that you didn’t want to waste our time on your rehab.
[Tsuzuri]
Yeah, but I didn’t say it like that.
[Megumi]
Huh? You did, though.
[Tsuzuri]
Gh–... Um…
[Megumi]
She said so, right, Kozu?
[Tsuzuri]
I remember her forcing a smile even though she looked like she was about to cry.
“You guys don’t need to–”
[Tsuzuri]
Okay, enough already! Why are you doing this!?
[Megumi]
Do something, Kozue!
Since you’ve been gone, I’ve had to deal with Tsuzuri on my own.
[Kozue]
And I’m sorry about that!
[Megumi]
Wait, no! I don’t have to apologize for that!
What are you two even here to say!?
[Megumi]
Well, in short…
[Kozue]
That was a year ago.
And we have already broken that promise the three of us made.
[Kozue]
Hmph… and you’re deciding that for me.
[Megumi]
Either way, I can’t do it.
I’m… I’m still…
[Megumi]
By the way, Megumi.
[Kozue]
Do you remember us talking about going on a training camp session at the beach before?
Eh? When was this...?
[Megumi]
Why don’t you come with us next week?
[Kozue]
…Huh!?
[Megumi]