Ooh.
[Tsuzuri]
That was...
[Kozue]
That was really good!
[Kaho]
I agree! You feel way more in sync than before!
[Sayaka]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s the best we’ve done so far.
It was perfect!
[Kaho]
Mmm…
[Tsuzuri]
We’re not quite perfect yet.
We’ve still got a long way to go.
[Tsuzuri]
That makes it sound like you’re doing poorly, though…
[Sayaka]
…I wonder…
[Kozue]
…Did I do well?
Yeah! You were really cool, Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho]
You’ve really improved.
Here, I recorded it, so you can check it for yourself.
[Sayaka]
I see…
[Kozue]
…You might be right.
We’re doing good.
[Tsuzuri]
Let’s keep at it.
There’s still more we can improve on.
[Tsuzuri]
True. We haven’t perfected the dance yet, so let’s thoroughly review that video later.
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
But I think we’ll be fine if we keep going at it like this.
Also, we still have to come up with choreography for Kaho-san and Murano-san.
[Kozue]
Oh, about that!
[Sayaka]
We came up with some choreography for ourselves.
[Kaho]
Wanna see it?
Huh!? You two came up with your own?
[Kozue]
Yes!
[Kaho & Sayaka]
Heh heh heh…
[Kaho]
I bet you two are surprised.
Since all of us will be performing, we decided to do our part and do what we could!
[Kaho]
So we came up with this!
Nice.
[Tsuzuri]
Good job, Kaho.
Yay!
[Kaho]
U-Um…
[Sayaka]
I worked hard too…
Yeah. Nice one, Saya.
[Tsuzuri]
Thank you!
[Sayaka]
Thank you both.
[Kozue]
Now we’ll have much more time for practice!
Yes!
[Kaho & Sayaka]
Next, we’ll have to sync up our choreography…
[Kozue]
Let’s make sure our performance is perfect before the Nadeshiko Festival!
That way, we can show everyone watching the festival a performance worthy of the School Idol Club!
[Kozue]
Let’s go!
[Kaho & Sayaka & Tsuzuri]
Oh?
[Kaho & Sayaka & Tsuzuri & Kozue]
Calling second-year student Otomune Kozue. Otomune Kozue.
[PA Announcement]
Please report to the student council room. Announcement over.
…What did you do, Kozu?
[Tsuzuri]
You’re already assuming she did something wrong!?
[Sayaka]
No way! I’ll go and apologize with you!
[Kaho]
I haven’t done anything wrong, and I will be going alone!
[Kozue]
You’re all making way too big a fuss over me getting called to go somewhere.
I-I’ll go instead!
[Kaho]
There’s no need.
[Kozue]
I’ll be fine.
Tsuzuri, could you watch over the practice for a moment?
[Kozue]
Sure.
[Tsuzuri]
I wonder why they’re calling you.
…I might have an idea.
[Kozue]
Anyway, I’ll tell you later.
And we were just getting into this…
[Tsuzuri]
It’s not like she’ll be gone for the rest of the day!
[Sayaka]
Let’s just keep doing our best, so we don’t worry Otomune-senpai later.
Oh, right!
[Kaho]
Please take good care of me, Tsuzuri-senpai!
Yeah, of course.
[Tsuzuri]
Why don’t we do some light exercises until Kozu comes back?
Good job, you two.
[Tsuzuri]
H-How was that…!
[Kaho]
That was… everything we’ve got!
I was really impressed.
[Tsuzuri]
The choreo you two came up with was really good.
Nice job coming up with it yourselves.
[Tsuzuri]
Haa… haa…
[Kaho]
Ehehe, we really did it, Sayaka-chan…
U-Um…
[Sayaka]
What is it?
[Tsuzuri]
I’m really happy, for real.
When you said you’d do your best for Kozu and me, I didn’t think you’d actually work this hard.
[Tsuzuri]
It’s… just…
[Sayaka]
What brought these compliments on…?
I thought about it while I was watching you two.
[Tsuzuri]
I realized you’ve been working so hard.
I’m happy to hear it, but…!
[Sayaka]
Um…
What happened to doing light exercises until Otomune-senpai comes back…?
[Sayaka]
Oh.
[Tsuzuri & Kaho]
Tsuzuri…
[Kozue]
What happened here…?
Sorry. I was so happy that I got too excited
[Tsuzuri]
The choreo they came up with was really good.
I see…
[Kozue]
I would have liked to see it, but I don’t think these two are in any condition to perform right now…
Can you stand?
[Kozue]
T-Thank you very much…!
[Kaho]
I’m okay. I can still keep going…!
I’m sorry… this is such a mess…
[Sayaka]
Don’t worry about it.
I’m glad to see that Tsuzuri’s very pleased.
[Kozue]
You two didn’t do anything wrong.
Did I do something wrong?
[Tsuzuri]
…I guess it’s my fault for getting called over.
[Kozue]
Oh, right! What happened there!?
[Kaho]
Are you alright, Kozue-senpai!?
Oh. It’s… nothing to worry about.
[Kozue]
What happened?
[Tsuzuri]
Like I said, it’s nothing to worry about.
[Kozue]
Are you not gonna tell us?
[Tsuzuri]
C-Calm down, maybe she just doesn’t want to tell us?
[Sayaka]
Maybe she was called over… because she made a mistake somewhere?
No, I didn’t…!
[Kozue]
Again, it’s really nothing to worry about.
Hm, how do I put this…
[Kozue]
You were scouted!?
[Kaho & Sayaka]
S-So basically, you were invited to transfer to another school!?
[Sayaka]
I was only invited to.
[Kozue]
My life is over!
[Kaho]
I’m going to wither as a flower bud!
Didn’t I say that I was only invited to?
[Kozue]
Don’t leave me!!
[Kaho]
It’s okay!
[Kozue]
Look, I’m not planning on leaving, so it’ll be okay.
So, um…
[Sayaka]
We really don’t need to worry about it, then?
I’m very honored that they requested me in particular to perform as a school idol with them, but…
[Kozue]
Ultimately, I get the final say on whether to accept or refuse.
That’s why there’s no need to worry like this. It was just an invitation.
[Kozue]
I see…
[Sayaka]
Oh, is that why you had a feeling you knew what you were being called for?
When I momentarily left the stall at the festival, a girl approached me and handed me a letter from her club.
[Kozue]
I had a feeling I was being called regarding that.
S-So… are you leaving me, Kozue-senpai…?
[Kaho]
No, no. I’ll be right here.
[Kozue]
…Are you sure you’re okay with that?
[Tsuzuri]
Huh?
[Kaho & Sayaka]
What… do you mean by that?
[Kozue]
I’ll ask again.
[Tsuzuri]
Are you sure you’re okay with refusing?
H-Huh…?
[Kozue]
Are you saying… I should consider their offer?
Have you fully considered it?
[Tsuzuri]
I don’t even need to.
[Kozue]
There’s no way I would leave Hasunosora.
I know full well what it feels like for other members to leave the club.
[Kozue]
I was the one who invited Kaho-san to join the club and formed the current iteration of Cerise Bouquet.
And more than anything, I decided that I would lead this club as its president.
[Kozue]
And at this point, even if I were to leave this school and join a new one,
there’s no guarantee I would take well to those new surroundings
[Kozue]
I don’t know if I would be proud to perform as a school idol for that school.
See? There was no reason for me to accept their offer from the very beginning.
[Kozue]
Fine. Then let me ask this…
[Tsuzuri]
Between that school’s School Idol Club and ours, which is more famous?
Setting aside past accomplishments and strictly speaking about how things are currently, theirs is.
[Kozue]
They regularly appear at nationals, and last year, they placed well…
This is their club.
[Kozue]
The girl in the middle is the one who invited me.
Oh, I’ve heard of these people before.
[Sayaka]
They’re famous for how in unison their performances are, right?
Right.
[Kozue]
To be frank, they’re quite amazing.
That’s what their School Idol Club is like.
[Kozue]
…Why do you ask?
So if you want to win Love Live!, you should join that club, then.
[Tsuzuri]
Tsuzuri… What are you trying to say?
[Kozue]
It’s almost like you want me to leave.
I don’t, but…
[Tsuzuri]
H-H-H-Hang on a minute!!
[Sayaka]
It’s not like Tsuzuri-senpai wants you to leave!!
Saya…
[Tsuzuri]
Our practice was going really well just now!
[Sayaka]
A-And I’m really looking forward to performing at my first school festival!
C-Come on, let’s practice…!
[Kaho]
Alright.
[Kozue]
…Let’s go, then.
[Tsuzuri]