Ahh… the hot water felt so nice…
[Kozue]
I’m sorry for using your bath before you…
Oh?
[Kozue]
Hello, is this Hasunosora-san?
[Tsuzuri]
Oh, I don’t need the “-san”?
Yes, this is Yugiri Tsuzuri.
[Tsuzuri]
It’s raining hard, so I’m at my house.
Kozu…
[Tsuzuri]
Otomune Kozue is here as well.
Is she doing what I think she is…?
[Kozue]
Diligently calling to inform the school…?
Yes, understood.
[Tsuzuri]
By tomorrow morning…
What time?
[Tsuzuri]
Return by 8:00, okay.
Okay then, seeya.
[Tsuzuri]
“Seeya”…!?
[Kozue]
Oh, Kozu. Are you finished?
[Tsuzuri]
Yes, I am. Thank you.
[Kozue]
I feel much warmer now.
But you know I would have been fine going after you, right?
[Kozue]
Nah, there was something I had to do.
[Tsuzuri]
Just now?
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
You have to call the dorms if you’re not coming back before curfew.
Did you know that?
[Tsuzuri]
Of course I knew that, but…
[Kozue]
You called in for me, too.
I’ve become a hard worker.
[Tsuzuri]
Right…
[Kozue]
You really have.
Because I couldn’t say anything to you back then.
[Tsuzuri]
What are you–?
[Kozue]
I’ve become an upperclassman now.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s right…
[Kozue]
You’re exactly right. We really have.
Listen, I’d feel guilty if you caught a cold.
[Kozue]
Hurry and take your bath now.
Aw…
[Tsuzuri]
But I always dreamed of sharing the bath at my house with one of my friends.
Then you shouldn’t have told me to go ahead!
[Kozue]
Mission failed.
[Tsuzuri]
Oh, you…
[Kozue]
Thank you, Kaho-san…
It looks like you had the right idea after all.
[Kozue]
But…
To think that this would happen again…
[Kozue]
Are those two alright…?
[Sayaka]
Oh, I just got a message!
[Kaho]
What did Otomune-senpai tell you!?
[Sayaka]
Hang on. Hang on–
[Kaho]
Hang on… Wait, I said!
I understand that you’re worried, but still!
[Kaho]
“We will be staying the night at Tsuzuri’s house.”
That’s a relief…
[Kaho]
I was so worried they’d force themselves to get back here even through all this heavy rain…
[Sayaka]
What, go all that way?
[Kaho]
There’s no way they would do that…
They wouldn’t, right?
[Kaho]
Ahaha… but see?
She’s still with Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho]
That’s right, but…
[Sayaka]
Oh, sorry!
Don’t worry about it.
[Kaho]
I have younger sisters, so I know what it’s like.
N-No, I can’t always be taking advantage of your hospitality.
[Sayaka]
I mean, I wouldn’t say “always”...
[Kaho]
Actually, usually I’m that one that’s–
It’s only thanks to your suggestion that they’re together, or that we’ll be performing as a full group, you know?
[Sayaka]
I mean, I guess, but wasn’t it your idea to send them to help out with the food stall?
[Kaho]
That was only because I happened to meet Reika-san earlier…
[Sayaka]
And besides.
I wonder if it really turned out okay. It’s raining so hard…
[Sayaka]
I-It’s not like the rain automatically means it went wrong!
[Kaho]
You know, it might even be a good thing! They ended up staying the night together at Tsuzuri-senpai’s house, right?
Alright, I’ll try to think of it that way.
[Sayaka]
There are still things we have to do, after all.
Yeah, let’s keep doing what we can for those two!
[Kaho]
Right.
[Sayaka]
Let’s do our best to perform as a full group!
[Kaho]
Right!
[Sayaka]
So right now, we don’t need to worry about them! They’ll be fine!
[Kaho]
Right…
[Sayaka]
Right?
Let’s do this!
[Kaho]
Go, go, let’s go–!
…Sayaka-chan?
[Kaho]
…I just remembered.
[Sayaka]
I didn’t wake her up yesterday or the day before yesterday.
Sayaka-chan!?
[Kaho]
I didn’t make her lunch, and I didn’t walk her to and from school.
[Sayaka]
So that should mean she’ll be fine without me, right!?
Huh? Does this mean I no longer have to worry about her?
[Sayaka]
Or am I just skirting my responsibility to her?
Wait, shouldn’t I be going to her right now, even though it’s raining?
[Sayaka]
Sayaka-chan!?
[Kaho]
Hey, calm down, Sayaka-chan!
Sayaka-chaaaan!!
[Kaho]
You asleep?
[Tsuzuri]
…Why are you even asking?
[Kozue]
This is the fourth time now.
Just wondering.
[Tsuzuri]
Yes, I’m asleep.
[Kozue]
If you really were asleep, you wouldn’t say you were…!
[Tsuzuri]
What do you want from me?
[Kozue]
There was something I wanted to say…
[Tsuzuri]
I’ve been trying to tell you, but it feels like someone’s stealing the words before they leave my mouth.
It’s been like this for a while now.
[Tsuzuri]
Today was really fun, huh?
Huh, did you fall asleep?
[Tsuzuri]
There’s no way I could after you said you wanted to tell me something.
[Kozue]
…I had fun today, yes.
Yeah. Um…
[Tsuzuri]
…I’m doing my best, too.
…Tsuzuri?
[Kozue]
…I don’t mean that you shouldn’t do your best.
[Tsuzuri]
I didn’t say this because I didn’t want to make you feel bad,
but… um…
[Tsuzuri]
I’m also doing my best.
So you shouldn’t feel like you need to do everything.
[Tsuzuri]
…Does it look like I’m overworking myself?
[Kozue]
No.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s not what I mean.
I just want to support you…
[Tsuzuri]
So I will. That’s what I wanted to say.
…Alright.
[Kozue]
Whoa–
[Tsuzuri]
…You move a lot in your sleep.
I’m not actually asleep.
[Kozue]
…I’m glad I finally said it.
[Tsuzuri]
What you just said?
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
I’ve always wanted to tell you.
So I’m glad I did.
[Tsuzuri]
…I’m glad you told me, too.
[Kozue]
…Hey, Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
You’re not hiding something, are you?
…Why do you ask?
[Kozue]
You don’t really say what you think.
[Tsuzuri]
Usually, I have to ask.
But…
[Tsuzuri]
…Recently, you haven’t really talked much about Love Live! either.
Really?
[Kozue]
…I guess so.
Then–
[Tsuzuri]
There are so many other things I’m doing.
[Kozue]
I’d be happy if you supported me through those.
…Really?
[Tsuzuri]
I’ll be counting on you, Tsuzuri.
[Kozue]
Okay.
[Tsuzuri]