Sachi-senpai… Megumi… Tsuzuri.
[Kozue]
What… What should I do here…?
Can’t sleep?
[Tsuzuri]
Tsuzuri…
[Kozue]
I don’t often see you awake at this hour, either.
Yeah…
[Tsuzuri]
Saya came over earlier.
…Actually, Kaho-san came to my dorm room earlier as well.
[Kozue]
Oh.
[Tsuzuri]
I assume they told us the same thing, then.
[Kozue]
Let’s perform as a full group of four! Together at the Nadeshiko Festival!
[Kaho]
I… I need some time to think about it.
[Kozue]
How did you respond, Tsuzuri?
I didn’t.
[Tsuzuri]
Well… I guess I just thanked her.
They care a lot about the two of us.
[Tsuzuri]
…I see.
[Kozue]
What about you, Kozu?
[Tsuzuri]
…I wasn’t sure myself.
That’s why I came here.
[Kozue]
…I think you should decide.
[Tsuzuri]
…Why?
[Kozue]
Because being a school idol isn’t something you should be forced into.
[Tsuzuri]
…Tsuzuri.
[Kozue]
I know.
[Tsuzuri]
We promised we wouldn’t stand on stage together again…
But we never said anything about performing as four, so…
[Tsuzuri]
You have a point.
[Kozue]
I suppose the rest is up to me, then.
…That song from back then.
[Kozue]
If I worked hard to perform that song one more time…
Maybe I could stand alongside you again.
[Kozue]
Alongside me?
[Tsuzuri]
I mean, I’d like it if you always stood alongside me.
But that song was…
[Tsuzuri]
This time… This time, we’ll do it properly.
[Kozue]
…O…kay.
[Tsuzuri]
Okay.
Hm?
[Kozue]
You’re right.
It’s different from before.
[Tsuzuri]
So I’m sure this will go better than before.
Right.
[Kozue]
We’re different than we were before…
I know that now.
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
Now we have Saya and Kaho.
And I’d like to respond to their feelings.
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
If we do that,
I’m sure I’ll finally be able to be a school idol with you this time.
[Tsuzuri]
I agree.
Let’s do this.
[Kozue]
Let’s try a four-member performance, then!
Wow…!
[Kaho]
We did it, Kaho-san!
[Sayaka]
Yeah!
[Kaho]
I have a request to make of you, in that case.
[Kozue]
See…
The thing is, there is a particular song I want to perform at this year’s Nadeshiko Festival.
[Kozue]
What kind of song is it?
[Kaho]
This song is… very difficult.
[Kozue]
It’s also the song that Tsuzuri and I performed at the Love Live! qualifiers.
I am ashamed to admit it, but I wasn’t able to perform it at a level where I would feel comfortable performing it with her.
[Kozue]
It’s a song we decided to never perform together again.
So…
[Kozue]
Then, we’ll just have to give it another try!
[Kaho]
Huh?
[Kozue]
I got this! Leave it to me!
[Kaho]
I’ll do everything to support you, Kozue-senpai!
Kaho-san…
[Kozue]
Let’s do it!
Are you in, Sayaka-chan!?
[Kaho]
Yes. We’ve come this far for our seniors, after all!
[Sayaka]
Kaho-san… Murano-san…
[Kozue]
Alright. I’ll… do my best.
Thanks.
[Tsuzuri]
If you didn’t suggest performing as a full group…
We wouldn’t have thought of trying this song again.
[Tsuzuri]
Yeah! Alright!
Let’s give it our best shot!
[Kaho]
Of course!
[Sayaka]
…Oh, Tsuzuri-senpai.
Yeah?
[Tsuzuri]
Could you tell me more about the song?
[Sayaka]
You too, Otomune-senpai…
You said it was a difficult song, so…
[Sayaka]
Yeah…
[Tsuzuri]
Alright, let’s start here, then.
Kozu, do you remember how the choreo went?
[Tsuzuri]
…Of course.
[Kozue]
Kaho-san, Murano-san, please watch this.
Sorta like that.
[Tsuzuri]
Wow…!
[Kaho]
It’s very… creative.
[Sayaka]
I’m not completely sure, but did Tsuzuri-senpai compose it?
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
Whoa… It’s a really cool song!
[Kaho]
Really? I’m happy to hear it, then.
[Tsuzuri]
Last year…
[Kozue]
Tsuzuri suddenly presented it to the club one day.
She said she thought she might have finished making a song.
[Kozue]
That sounds like something she would do.
[Sayaka]
All I could think of then…
[Tsuzuri]
Was that I wanted to do my best together with Kozu.
…I failed to meet your expectations, though.
[Kozue]
But that’s why I wanted to try again, one more time.
The choreography is very extensive, yet there are still so many subtle details…
[Sayaka]
I can clearly see how this would be very difficult to perform.
Huh? Was what you just did not good enough?
[Kaho]
Yes.
Yeah.
No hesitation at all!?
[Kaho]
Is this what you meant by not being in sync?
[Sayaka]
You know, I did notice that something felt a little off…
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
In any case, one of my deepest regrets is that we never managed to perfect our performance of this song.
[Kozue]
So…
I really want to get it right this time.
[Kozue]
Alright, I get it!
[Kaho]
So first, we need to work on getting in sync, right?
Let’s do this, Sayaka-chan!
[Kaho]
R-Right.
[Sayaka]
You know I can handle anything, but have you come up with something, Kaho-san?
Yeah!
Alright, I’ll go first!
[Kaho]
Kozue-senpai, Tsuzuri-senpai.
You said you were having problems getting in sync, right?
[Kaho]
Y-Yes. I mentioned that, but…
[Kozue]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
Then…
[Kaho]
You should stick together real close until you get it!
‘Kay.
[Tsuzuri]
Is that what you meant…?
[Sayaka]
Just like that!
[Kaho]
Huh!?
[Kozue]
I have two younger sisters, you know!
[Kaho]
And they’re always together, so they’re real close!
So…?
[Sayaka]
So!
[Kaho]
As long as you’re together, you’ll definitely understand each other better….
And you’ll get closer and closer!
[Kaho]
…F-For how long?
[Kozue]
Forever!
[Kaho]
I… see…
[Sayaka]
Otomune-senpai, Tsuzuri-senpai can be a real handful, so… good luck.
A-Are we really doing this!?
[Kozue]
I can be a real handful, so good luck.
[Tsuzuri]
…A-Alright, fine. I said I’d trust those two, so…
[Kozue]
If they think we need this, I guess we’ll just have to do it!
There’s no way this will work.
[Kozue]
No way!
[Kaho]
We have to come up with something else as fast as we can!
[Sayaka]
Yeah, you’re right, Sayaka-chan!
Let’s figure something out!
[Kaho]
Did you hate it, Kozu?
[Tsuzuri]
I-I didn’t hate it…
[Kozue]
But at the very least, it’s dangerous for us to be that close during practice, so I think we should stop.
I agree with that…
[Sayaka]
Hm…
[Kaho]
Okay. I’ll allow it, then.
T-Thank you…?
[Kozue]
And we can’t just ignore our dance lessons.
They’re very important.
[Sayaka]
This is hard…
[Tsuzuri]
Well, even though physically getting closer wasn’t the best idea…
[Sayaka]
Wait, it wasn’t!?
[Kaho]
I do agree that you need to be emotionally closer to get in sync.
[Sayaka]
How should we do that?
[Tsuzuri]
Hm, well…
[Sayaka]
This is just a thought, but maybe if you had a conversation with each other and discussed your worries,
then you’ll be able to do something you couldn’t before… probably.
[Sayaka]
Personally, there are a lot of things I haven’t told you about, Tsuzuri-senpai.
Things like what I worry about my figure skating, for example.
[Sayaka]
Kozu, is something worrying you?
[Tsuzuri]
Nothing in particular…
[Kozue]
Alright, done.
[Tsuzuri]
That’s not what I meant!
[Sayaka]
…Ahem.
Anyway, um…
[Sayaka]
I know you’re already working so hard, but there was something I wanted to talk to you two about.
What could it be?
Is it something for the article?
[Kozue]
Oh, no, that’s already done.
[Sayaka]
I wanted to have you check on it before the Nadeshiko Festival,
but right now, there’s something more important I need you two for.
[Sayaka]
And that’s this!
[Kaho]
A festival?
[Tsuzuri]
It’s nearly summer, so it’s about that time of year when shrines start holding these kinds of events, huh?
[Kozue]
Did you want all of us to go together?
No, actually.
[Sayaka]
The thing is, I met up with Reika-san this morning.
Oh, Reika-san. Haven’t talked to her in a while.
[Tsuzuri]
It sounded like she needed more part-timers to help her out. So…
[Sayaka]
We were hoping you’d go help out!
[Kaho]
Wait, us…?
[Kozue]
Yeah! Actually, I already said that you two would go over!
[Kaho]
You already did…!?
[Kozue]
Yes.
[Sayaka]
She even said she was looking forward to it.
I see…
[Kozue]
Um…
[Sayaka]
We’re sorry that we’re forcing you into this!
[Kaho]
…No, it’s fine.
[Kozue]
Actually, I probably should be thanking you.
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
Thanks, you two.
Anyway!
[Sayaka]
Kozue-senpai, Tsuzuri-senpai, see you later!
[Kaho]
Have a nice trip!