Tsuzuri!
[Kozue]
…Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
…There’s… something I have to tell you…
[Kozue]
…What?
[Tsuzuri]
It’s not like I don’t have anything to say to you, but…
I haven’t changed my mind from earlier.
[Tsuzuri]
No matter–
I know.
[Kozue]
You were completely right.
Then…
[Tsuzuri]
What are you going to do?
Are you going… to that other school?
[Tsuzuri]
…I was mistaken.
[Kozue]
What was most important to me was becoming a praiseworthy school idol,
winning Love Live!, and protecting the legacy of the Hasunosora School Idol Club.
[Kozue]
That’s why I intended to reject the scouting offer…
and why I decided to change our choreography.
[Kozue]
You said that earlier.
[Tsuzuri]
I know.
[Kozue]
That’s why I said I was mistaken.
I was wrong.
[Kozue]
I know that now.
Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
What are you trying to say?
Tsuzuri, I…
[Kozue]
…I didn’t want to be separated from you.
…Huh?
[Tsuzuri]
I’ve had such an enjoyable experience in this club.
[Kozue]
We had seniors I looked up to and delightful friends to be with.
Even if we came to lose some of those…
[Kozue]
…Of all that I aspired to be when we first met, you’re all that’s left.
Huh…?
[Tsuzuri]
I’m no longer pretending to be strong.
[Kozue]
I never even realized how I truly felt.
Kozu…
[Tsuzuri]
But… you’re…
This has nothing to do with being scouted.
[Kozue]
Please forget those excuses I gave earlier…
And listen to how I truly feel.
[Kozue]
I just… don’t want to leave you all.
And back then…
[Kozue]
I didn’t want you to leave me.
That’s why I don’t want to go anywhere.
[Kozue]
…My dream is no longer just my own.
It’s a dream we want to fulfill together.
[Kozue]
So…
I want to make that dream come true, right here!
[Kozue]
Is that…
[Tsuzuri]
How you really…?
I’m sorry I haven’t said any of this before now.
[Kozue]
I’m so sorry…
…The words I wanted to say, and the words I should have said all along…
[Kozue]
Until just now, I never realized what they were.
So… what do you say?
[Kozue]
I’m sure that I’m no longer lying to myself…
Or at least, I think so.
[Kozue]
…Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
I finally hear your true feelings.
…I’m happy that you do.
[Kozue]
Sorry, Kozu…
[Tsuzuri]
You have nothing to apologize for.
[Kozue]
No…
[Tsuzuri]
All I knew was that you were hiding something from me at the qualifiers.
I should have asked.
[Tsuzuri]
Maybe if I had…
…Maybe.
[Kozue]
…I should have told you.
Even though my reason was selfish.
[Kozue]
Kozue-senpaaaai!
[Kaho]
Tsuzuri-senpai!
[Sayaka]
Oh, my… if it isn’t the knot that ties us together.
[Kozue]
Ties us…?
[Tsuzuri]
I’d rather you didn’t cut it off there…
[Kozue]
We’re over here, you two!
Apologies for the wait.
[Kozue]
But thanks to you two, everything’s okay now!
Wait… you still can’t trust my “okay”s, huh…
[Kozue]
I… how do I say this…?
Ahaha, don’t worry, we get it, Kozue-senpai!
[Kaho]
You’re saying that things are all okay between you two now, right?
I’m really happy to see it.
[Sayaka]
I… couldn’t find Tsuzuri-senpai, so I was getting really worried.
Sorry.
[Tsuzuri]
But I feel better now.
Okay.
[Sayaka]
I’m sorry for worrying you two.
[Kozue]
I’m very grateful for your help.
Ehehe…
[Kaho]
…Of course.
[Sayaka]
But now I’m sure we can have the best performance ever.
[Tsuzuri]
I agree.
[Kozue]
I feel I can perform that song perfectly now.
After all… our feelings are now all as one.
[Kozue]
Alright!
[Kaho]
Looks like everything’s coming together perfectly!
Kozue-senpai, lead us back into it!
[Kaho]
Me?
[Kozue]
…I think it would be quite awkward if I led you all at this moment…
Just do things as you normally would.
[Sayaka]
Yeah.
[Tsuzuri]
I believe in you.
Alright, fine.
[Kozue]
Then…
Starting tomorrow, let’s do our best to practice for the Nadeshiko Festival!
[Kozue]
That way, we can show everyone watching the festival a performance worthy of the School Idol Club–
No…
[Kozue]
Because I want to have the best performance, together with all of you!