Those two even went and got permission for us to leave the school…
[Kozue]
They’re far more cunning than I give them credit for.
Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
Oh, I’m sorry.
What is it?
[Kozue]
Heeey! Over here, over here!
[Reika-san]
Let’s go.
[Tsuzuri]
Right.
[Kozue]
So basically, I ended up having to run three stalls all by myself!
[Reika-san]
Could you two please handle this one for me!?
H-How did this happen?
[Kozue]
The festival was short on manpower, so some stalls came to me for help.
[Reika-san]
Before I knew it, I realized I needed some help too!
I see you haven’t changed at all, Reika-san…
[Kozue]
Okay, leave it to us.
Thanks, Kozue-chan!
[Reika-san]
Oh, sorry about this, Tsuzuri-chan!
No prob. I’m good at tending stores.
[Tsuzuri]
Thank you, thank you!
[Reika-san]
Alright, I’ll be… go… ing…?
Wait, why are you two standing so close to each other?
[Reika-san]
Well… uh…
[Kozue]
It’s a trial.
[Tsuzuri]
Huh…?
[Reika-san]
Well, it has been a while since I last saw you two together, and it’s pretty interesting, so oh well!
Alright, then, I’m really grateful for the help!
[Reika-san]
Sorry about all this! I’ll come by every now and then to check up on you two!
By the way, Kozu, what kind of stall are we handling?
[Tsuzuri]
You accepted without knowing what we’re in charge of, huh…
[Kozue]
There. Apologies for the wait.
We hope you’ll come stop by again.
[Kozue]
Bye-bye~
[Tsuzuri]
Kozu, am I doing enough?
I understand where you’re coming from,
[Kozue]
but it would be dangerous for both of us to work the machine at the same time in such a small space.
Besides, we aren’t busy enough to need to do that.
[Kozue]
Oh, okay.
[Tsuzuri]
There’s not a lot of customers, huh.
Well, it happens.
[Kozue]
So, Tsuzuri…
I wouldn’t want to report to Reika-san that there weren’t many customers today.
[Kozue]
You want to try to make today a success too, right?
Hm? Yeah…
[Tsuzuri]
Why don’t we… discuss ways to attract customers to the stall?
[Kozue]
It’s my first time working at a stall like this, so I want to serve as many customers as I can.
Alright, I’ll do my best to come up with something.
[Tsuzuri]
Kozu, stay here and gird yourself for when the customers arrive.
I… don’t think “gird” is the right word here…
[Kozue]
But I understand. I’ll start preparing things.
Alright, let’s see…
[Tsuzuri]
…Ah.
Hm? Have you thought of something?
[Kozue]
Yeah… Keep the music going.
[Tsuzuri]
…Music?
[Kozue]
Gah… Ah… Kozue-chan… Tsuzuri-chan… I’m here to help…?
[Reika-san]
No way, they’ve got so many customers.
Is that…?
[Reika-san]
We gave it everything we’ve got.
[Tsuzuri]
Here you go! Thank you for your purchase!
[Kozue]
…Ah! I gotta get back!
[Reika-san]
Kozue-chaaan! Tsuzuri-chaaan!
We have lots of ice back at the main stall, so use as much as you want!
[Reika-san]
But you know… hehe,
I’m really glad I asked those two to help out.
[Reika-san]
I can’t believe we’re using up all our ingredients this quickly.
[Kozue]
We’re selling so much, all thanks to Tsuzuri’s presentation.
I’m sure this much should be enough for the rest of the festival.
[Kozue]
Okay, let’s head back now.
Oh, you there, excuse me.
[School Idol from Another School]
Are you perhaps Otomune Kozue-san?
…You’re…
[Kozue]
Oh, I knew it!
[School Idol from Another School]
O-oh, no, wait.
You’re working at the moment, right, Kozue-san?
[School Idol from Another School]
I came here to deliver this, so please accept it.
And this is…?
[Kozue]
You seem busy at the moment, but please let me know your response later.
[School Idol from Another School]
Your stall today seems wonderful, so… good luck!
Alright, then…
[School Idol from Another School]
T-Thank you very much…
[Kozue]
That girl just now must have been…
No, before that, I should read this letter.
[Kozue]
…What?
Kozu.
[Tsuzuri]
…Oh, Tsuzuri!
[Kozue]
Yes, what is it?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
[Tsuzuri]
I just kinda felt you were like an empty lunch box there.
…No, not at all.
[Kozue]
There’s still plenty left in me.
Half-empty, then?
[Tsuzuri]
Interesting word choice...
[Kozue]
Anyway, I think I’m just getting tired.
We’re still in the middle of working, but I’m already starting to lose focus…
[Kozue]
Oh?
What’s going on?
[Tsuzuri]
I think Reika-san should be here soon.
Oh, no. The numbers aren’t adding up…
[Kozue]
It wasn’t me.
[Tsuzuri]
No one said that, though…
[Kozue]
I think I’ll just have to recount this.
I can take care of the rest with Reika-san, so why don’t you go ahead and head back?
[Kozue]
Huh?
[Tsuzuri]
Hm?
[Kozue]
…You know I like math, right?
[Tsuzuri]
Math…
[Kozue]
Oh, it’s okay. If I need to, I’ll just use the calculator on my phone.
No need to worry.
[Kozue]
…Tsuzuri?
Is it different this time…?
[Tsuzuri]
Hm? What is?
[Kozue]
I thought we would tackle this issue together too.
[Tsuzuri]
…You’re right. You really helped me out there earlier.
[Kozue]
Okay, then… I’ll leave half to you.
‘Kay.
[Tsuzuri]
Last year…
I would always head back first.
[Tsuzuri]
I remember.
[Kozue]
That was fine, though.
But…
[Tsuzuri]
I just thought that this might be better.
…I see.
[Kozue]
Maybe it wasn’t better after all…
[Tsuzuri]
I-I was really happy, though.
[Kozue]
Really? It was a good thing, then.
[Tsuzuri]
We managed to fix the problem, after all.
[Kozue]
…But at this rate, we’ll be drenched by the time we make it back to the dorms.
Climbing up the mountain trail would be hard.
[Tsuzuri]
I-I wasn’t planning on walking back…
[Kozue]
S-Sorry! I didn’t think this would happen!
[Reika-san]
N-No, it’s fine. Please come inside.
[Kozue]
I’m really sorry!
[Reika-san]
I’ll take responsibility for this and personally drive you back…!
Reika-san, don’t you own a really small scooter…?
[Tsuzuri]
…I’ll personally drive you back!
[Reika-san]
There’s no way we would fit!
[Kozue]
B-But, how would I make it up to you two…
[Reika-san]
Oh.
[Tsuzuri]
Tsuzuri?
[Kozue]
Wanna come over to my place, Kozu?
[Tsuzuri]